music
音楽
In the Central Research Institute,
中央研究所では、
the lecture will begin on August 4th.
講義は8月4日に始まります。
Please welcome Wang Huijun, the Deputy Director of the Dean of the Department of Education.
教育学部長副部長の王恵軍氏を歓迎します。
applause
拍手
Dear friends and colleagues,
親愛なる友人や同僚の皆様、
I AM Wang Hui Jun.
私は王輝君です。
Thank you very much for coming to this feast of knowledge
この知識の饗宴にご来場いただきまして誠にありがとうございます
The feast of knowledge in the Central Plains has a history of many years
中原の知識の饗宴には長い歴史がある
There have always been very, very good speakers to give us incisive speeches in simple terms
簡単な言葉で鋭いスピーチをしてくれる、非常に優れた講演者が常に存在します。
Here I want to remind me that after the speech is over, the next time will be announced
ここで念のため言っておきますが、講演終了後に次回の開催が発表されます。
I think it's better to announce it first, or I will forget later
先に発表したほうがいいと思います、そうしないと後で忘れてしまいます
Therefore, the feast of knowledge in September is organized by Associate Researcher Lei Xianglin
したがって、9月の知識の饗宴は、准研究員の雷香林によって企画されます。
Our Institute of Modern History of the Central Plains
私たちの中部平野近現代史研究所
He's going to give a lecture that has something to do with life.
彼は人生に関わる講義をするつもりだ。
Due to the meaning of Du Congming
杜聡明の意味により
The Mystery of Du Congming's Chinese Medicine Research
杜崇明の中医学研究の謎
Traditional Medical Sciences and Modernity in East Asia
東アジアの伝統医学と近代性
So it must have been a pretty good speech.
ということは、かなり良いスピーチだったのではないでしょうか。
So please come to participate in September
9月はぜひご参加ください
I am very happy to invite you to the feast of knowledge in the Central Plains today
本日はセントラルプレーンズの知識の饗宴にご招待できることを大変うれしく思います
Institute of Molecular Biology
分子生物研究所
We all have a branch office
私たちは皆、支店を持っています
early annullosis
分生所早期
Why is it called split life?
なぜスプリットライフと呼ばれるのでしょうか？
Because wife and husband are often
妻や夫はよくあるので、
live in a different place
別の場所に住んでいます
So either the wife is in the US
つまり、妻が米国にいるかのどちらかです
Or the wife is in Taiwan
それとも奥さんが台湾にいるのか
So this branch office was established around 1988
この支店は1988年頃に設立されました。
So it has a history of more than 20 years and almost 30 years
20年以上、30年近い歴史があります。
Our Sun Yihan designated researcher
当社指定研究員 Sun Yihan
Is that time to come into the branch office
支店に来る時間ですか
In the early days, I also participated in the establishment of some branch offices
初期の頃は、私もいくつかの支社の設立に参加しました。
Dr. Sun Yihan
孫宜翰博士
What he writes here is very interesting
彼がここで書いていることは非常に興味深いです
He said he graduated from Hsinchu Middle School
新竹中学校を卒業したそうです
In 1974, he gave up the medical department of National Taiwan University
1974年、国立台湾大学医学部を中退。
Then the first choice was to enter the Department of Botany, National Taiwan University
そこで第一志望は国立台湾大学植物学部への入学でした。
I don't know why you do this kind of thing
なぜこのようなことをするのか分かりません
but anyway
とにかく
But I also gave up on this
でもこれも諦めた
I don't have a medical degree from National Taiwan University
私は国立台湾大学で医学の学位を取得していません
I said that at that time, I heard that the score seemed to be able to enter Kaohsiung Medical University.
その時は高雄医科大学に入学できそうな点数だったそうですと話しました。
But I didn't read one either
でも私も一冊も読んでなかった
I went to study chemistry
化学を勉強しに行きました
Anyway, after he graduates
とにかく卒業したら
After graduation in Taiwan
台湾卒業後
to America's top universities
アメリカの一流大学へ
Caltech to do research in biology
カリフォルニア工科大学が生物学の研究を行う
biological research over there
向こうの生物学研究
Caltech I also took
私も受験したカリフォルニア工科大学
that very small school
あのとても小さな学校
But all professors are top professors
でも教授はみんな一流の教授だよ
Who is Mr. Anyway?
とにかくミスターって誰ですか？
Leah Wood
リア・ウッド
Leah Wood is also a very legendary figure
リア・ウッドも非常に伝説的な人物です
Maybe wait a minute, Mr. Sun can introduce us
ちょっと待ってください、孫さんが私たちを紹介してくれるかもしれません
Like the sequencing of this modern DNA
この現代の DNA の配列決定のように
Also developed by Leah Wood
こちらもリア・ウッド氏が開発した
commercialize it
それを商品化する
So Mr. Sun at Caltech
カリフォルニア工科大学のサン氏
After a very solid training
非常に充実したトレーニングを経て、
Go to 125th University as a postdoctoral fellow
第125大学に博士研究員として進学
It's been a while
しばらく経ちました
He returned to Taiwan in 1988
1988年に台湾に帰国
Join us as an associate researcher
准研究員として参加しましょう
that he made very contact
彼がとても連絡を取ったということ
but you can tell
しかし、あなたは言うことができます
He did not become a professor in three years
彼は3年たっても教授になれなかった
why do you know
なぜ知っていますか
Because Mr. Sun is very rigorous in running the academy
孫先生はアカデミーの運営にとても厳格だから
he must do
彼はしなければならない
Either do the best or don't do it
最善を尽くすか、やらないかのどちらかです
So he worked hard
それで彼は一生懸命働きました
to make these studies very touching
これらの研究を非常に感動的なものにするために
That's a coincidence too
それも偶然ですね
After our recent Dean Liao Junzi came back
最近の廖君子学部長が戻ってきてから
He just emphasized that we should plant but not quantity
彼はただ、植えるべきではあるが量ではないと強調しただけだ
In the past, everyone was aiming at a lot of papers
昔はみんなたくさんの論文を狙っていた
But that plant is not so good
でもその植物はあまり良くない
What Taiwan lacks now is high-quality research
今台湾に欠けているのは質の高い研究だ
Whether it is innovation
それがイノベーションなのかどうか
or to have a lot of this
またはこれをたくさん持つこと
How do you say this in basic research?
基礎研究ではどう言うのでしょうか？
Guide to the updated field
更新されたフィールドのご案内
So Mr. Sun is the cultural hygiene in this area
つまり、孫氏はこの地域の文化衛生の責任者なのです
he did very well
彼はとてもよくやった
However, in addition to doing a good job in this research, he
しかし、彼はこの研究で良い仕事をしただけでなく、
Twenty or twenty years ago, he was known as our so-called Special Review Researcher
二十年か二十年前、彼はいわゆる特別審査研究員として知られていました。
That's a very rare thing
それはとても珍しいことです
Teacher Sun has been using this fruit fly
サン先生はこのショウジョウバエを使っています
He just told me the reason why his eyes are red
彼は目が赤い理由を教えてくれました
wait a minute and he'll explain it to us
ちょっと待ってください、そうすれば彼が私たちに説明してくれるでしょう
Drosophila was used very early to create what we call animal models
ショウジョウバエは、私たちが動物モデルと呼ぶものを作成するために非常に早くから使用されました。
Actually, you already talked about using animal mode once
実はアニマルモードを使うことについてはすでに一度話していたんです
A few years ago, it seemed that there was a self-made response
数年前は自作自演があったようです
Today we are going to talk about the fruit fly
今日はショウジョウバエについてお話します
I just saw that fruit fly and I figured it has six legs
今そのショウジョウバエを見たんだけど、足が6本あるのだと思った
I asked him why
私は彼にその理由を尋ねました
what are those eight legs
その8本の足は何ですか
He said spiders have eight legs
彼はクモには8本の足があると言った
Fruit flies are something different
ショウジョウバエは何か違う
fruit flies are insects
ショウジョウバエは昆虫です
what is a spider
蜘蛛とは何ですか
anyway so do I really understand
とにかく、私は本当に理解していますか
But the fruit fly because of its disease model
しかし、ショウジョウバエにはその病気モデルがあるため、
or wait for the creation
または作成を待ちます
has been around for many years
何年も前から存在している
it has something to say
それは何か言いたいことがある
has several nobel prizes
ノーベル賞をいくつか受賞している
from the study of fruit flies
ショウジョウバエの研究から
especially genetically
特に遺伝的に
it requires understanding of development
開発についての理解が必要です
words of development biology
発生生物学
Drosophila is indispensable
ショウジョウバエは欠かせない
There are quite a lot of people who make fruit flies in our country
私たちの国にはショウジョウバエをやっている人がかなりたくさんいます
There are also very touching
とても感動的なものもあります
There is a group of people in our Central Plains Institute
私たちのセントラルプレーンズ研究所には人々のグループがあります
Animals that specialize in different disease models
さまざまな疾患モデルに特化した動物
for neural research
神経研究用
This Teacher Sun is a teacher in this field
この孫先生はこの分野の先生です
He leads a group in our Central Plains Academy
彼はセントラル プレーンズ アカデミーのグループを率いています
specialized in neuroscience research
神経科学研究を専門とする
Our English name is NPASS
英語名は NPASS です
Neuroscience Program at the Academia Cineca
アカデミア・シネカの神経科学プログラム
This laboratory with thirty or forty researchers is participating in this program
30～40人の研究者がいるこの研究室はこのプログラムに参加しています
Our Teacher Sun has led this group of people from the very beginning
私たちのサン先生は最初からこのグループを率いてきました
So he plays a very important role in neuroscience in Taiwan
つまり、彼は台湾の神経科学において非常に重要な役割を果たしているのです。
A pusher in many fields
さまざまな分野で活躍する推進者
So he has won many awards
それで彼は多くの賞を受賞しています
I have seen this young researcher's book award
この若手研究者の図書賞を見てきました
This is very rare in Academia Sinica
これは中央研究院では非常に珍しいことです
NSC End-of-Research Award
NSC研究成果賞
Ministry of Education Academic Awards
文部科学省学術賞
This is already top in our Academia Sinica
これはすでに中央研究院でトップです
Because we can't take the award as the professor's award here
ここで賞を教授賞として受け取ることはできないので
Hou Jindui, etc.
ホウ・ジンドゥイなど
so many honors
たくさんの栄誉
But what I admire most about him is
しかし、私が彼について最も尊敬しているのは、
His spirit of public service is very important
彼の公共奉仕の精神は非常に重要です
very very rare
とてもとても珍しい
He was the convener of the Biology Department of our National Science Council
彼は米国科学会議の生物学部の招集者でした
Then in our TCM Hospital Academic Consulting Association
そして私たち中医院学術コンサルティング協会では
Also served as our Deputy Executive Secretary for Life Sciences
ライフサイエンス担当副事務局長も務めた
A while ago, he also became the vice-chairman of the National Science Council.
少し前に、彼は国家学術会議の副会長にも就任した。
that is very difficult
それはとても難しいです
That's in the vice-chairman's tenure
それは副会長の任期中です
He also promotes these recombinations of these biological
彼はまた、これらの生物学的要素の組み換えを促進します。
So contribute a lot
だからたくさん貢献してね
Recently, of course, the Ministry of Science and Technology has a neuroscience project
もちろん最近、科学技術省は神経科学プロジェクトを立ち上げました。
he is our convener
彼は私たちの招集者です
So today he is going to tell us some research about the fruit camp
今日は彼がフルーツキャンプについての研究について話してくれる予定です
In addition to their very touch
彼らのタッチそのものに加えて、
He will introduce other relevant
彼は他の関連するものを紹介します
So his topic "Little Fruit Builds a Great Communist Party"
彼のテーマは「小さな果物で偉大な共産党を築く」
The contribution of this fruit camp to human development and disease research
人類の発達と病気の研究に対するこのフルーツキャンプの貢献
what the hell
なんてこったい
so welcome to take care of the teacher
先生をよろしくお願いします
Soft Block Mineral Gaster
ソフトブロックミネラルガスター
Mineral Gaster Gaster
ミネラルガスターガスター
So we divide it into AQ
したがって、それをAQに分割します
that is also called wind
それは風とも呼ばれます
The fruit flies like this are what you usually think of
あなたが通常思い浮かべるのはこのようなショウジョウバエです
the kind that endangers business
ビジネスを危険にさらす種類
Chinese style
中方國式
Then the inner class feels different
そうすると内層の感覚が違う
Fruit flies coexist with humans
ショウジョウバエは人間と共生する
as long as someone is in one place
誰かがひとつの場所にいる限り
or in spark water
または火花水の中で
can see
見える
eat rotten fruit
腐った果物を食べる
so it doesn't harm us humans
それは私たち人間に害を及ぼすものではありません
Doesn't it carry anything on it that affects what
何に影響を与えるものは何も載っていないのですか
or some of our accelerated
または私たちの加速されたものの一部
Then it can also take anything
それなら何でも取れる
Will affect the fruits and watercolors you think it doesn't hurt us
あなたが私たちに害を及ぼさないと思っている果物や水彩画に影響を与えるでしょう
it eats rotten fruit
それは腐った果物を食べます
has rotted
腐ってしまった
But such a
しかし、そのような
it is at...
それは...にあります
Its life is very fierce
その生涯は非常に熾烈です
from a city from
ある都市から
hold very poor mating
非常に悪い嵌合を保持します
It should have a setting on it
設定があるはずです
This platform is below our normal temperature at 25 degrees
このプラットフォームの温度は通常の 25 度より低いです
Just give it a piece a day
1日1粒だけ与えるだけです
Then it will go through 30% to 60% of the period
その後、期間の 30% ～ 60% が経過します。
Then it will separate its exoskeleton
それから外骨格を分離します
Do not return it and then make an impression
返品せずに印象を残してください
then just give it life
それから命を与えてください
Life in this fruit camp is very interesting
このフルーツキャンプでの生活はとても興味深いです
Here we emphasize that its development
ここで私たちが強調したいのは、その開発が
I will tell the temperature
温度を伝えます
Because insects it is not like we are cross-temperature
昆虫だから、私たちは温度を超えているわけではない
so the temperature inside its body
それで体内の温度は
changes with the outside temperature
外気温によって変化する
so the temperature is higher
だから気温が高くなります
Its whole development process will be faster
開発プロセス全体が高速化されます
The lower the temperature, the slower its growth
気温が低いと成長が遅くなる
So we can use temperature to adjust
したがって、温度を調整することができます
Then its life is probably normal
そうすれば、その人生はおそらく正常です
We can be between 16 degrees and 30 degrees
気温は16度から30度の間になります
can raise it
それを上げることができます
So we're talking about 25 degrees here
ここでは25度について話しています
On that day, the embryo will be skinned.
その日、胎児の皮が剥かれます。
Then one day after another
それから、ある日、また次の日
Twenty Another Bug Day
二十もう虫の日
Three Zeros and Worms have three days
3 つのゼロとワームには 3 日あります
The only thing it has to do at this point
この時点でやるべきことはただ一つ
Just eat in the food
食べ物の中で食べるだけ
So its behavior is backlight
したがって、その動作は逆光です
then to the ground
それから地面へ
It burrows into that fruit and eats it
その果実に穴を掘って食べる
When it arrives, its body grows
到着すると体が大きくなります
In the late period of the three zeros and worms
スリーゼロとワームの後期
it has a huge transformation
それは大きな変化を持っています
Its behavior changed, it became like a light background
挙動が変わり、背後に光が差したようになった
it crawls out of the food
食べ物から這い出てくる
then find a clean place
それからきれいな場所を見つけてください
its shell hardens
殻が硬くなる
Then it starts to form a yong
それからヨンを形成し始めます
that's in this yong
それはこのヨンの中にある
Its entire body was almost completely knocked out and redone
全身がほぼ完全に破壊され、作り直されている
Many of these heavy cells are dying
これらの重い細胞の多くが死にかけています
Then part of the cells start to rebuild a body
その後、細胞の一部が体を再構築し始めます
so we call it a complete metamorphosis
だから私たちはそれを完全変態と呼んでいます
Because the individual that grew up
成長した個体だから
It's totally different from heavy
重いのとは全然違います
That's the same thing as a caterpillar turning into a butterfly
それは芋虫が蝶になるのと同じこと
So what about this life history?
では、この人生史はどうでしょうか？
it basically develops twice
基本的に2回展開します
first time its in a short time
初めて、短時間で
In a day it makes a heavy body
一日で体が重くなる
It can move, eat, and perform various behaviors
動いたり、食べたり、さまざまな行動をすることができます
Then when it's time to kill and redo
そして、キルしてやり直すときが来たら
long a completely different
長い間完全に違う
it's late
遅いです
Chest is about five days
胸は5日くらい
Then he will open the chest shell
それから彼はこの胸の殻を開けるでしょう
he has a sac on his head
彼は頭に嚢を持っています
He'll beat his bodily fluids into the sac
彼は体液を嚢の中に叩き込むだろう
There is a bag on the head
頭に袋が載ってます
Then let him break through the cover on the chest
それから彼に胸のカバーを突き破らせてください
then he crawled out
それから彼は這い出てきた
crawled out with his wings tucked together
翼を閉じて這い出た
Then he slowly spread his wings
それから彼はゆっくりと羽を広げた
then become a mature individual
それから成熟した個人になる
What about the adult worm that hatched like this?
このようにして孵化した成虫はどうなるでしょうか？
It takes about 12 hours to believe that they are mature enough to mate
交尾できるほど成熟したと信じるには約12時間かかります
and then the next generation
そして次の世代へ
So very interesting life history of a
非常に興味深い人生史
Why do we use fruit flies as materials
なぜショウジョウバエを材料として使うのか
Then we are now doing research on many organisms
それから私たちは今、多くの生物の研究を行っています
A very important center is the gene
非常に重要な中心は遺伝子です
The fruit flies are being studied because
ショウジョウバエが研究されている理由は、
He can easily find genetic mutations
彼は遺伝子変異を簡単に見つけることができる
his genes can
彼の遺伝子はできる
we can do screening
スクリーニングを行うことができます
Well, any living thing can mutate
まあ、どんな生き物でも突然変異する可能性はあります。
However, the probability of mutation is usually not high
ただし、通常、突然変異の確率は高くありません
Not high, about one thousandth of a thousandth
それほど高くはなく、1000分の1程度
Let's say one in ten thousand
1万分の1としましょう
You need 10,000 fruit flies
10,000匹のショウジョウバエが必要です
you can pick a mutant
ミュータントを選ぶことができる
is what you want
それはあなたが望むものです
If it is a mouse
マウスなら
You need 10,000 mice
10,000 個のマウスが必要です
Then this is huge and expensive
それから、これは巨大で高価です
If you want to use elephants
象を使うなら
Those 10,000 elephants are unlikely to be able to conduct experiments
この 10,000 頭のゾウでは実験ができる可能性は低い
So Drosophila is a multicellular organism
つまり、ショウジョウバエは多細胞生物です
easier to feed
餌を与えやすい
Its life cycle is short
ライフサイクルが短い
Can give birth to many at a time
一度にたくさん産むことができる
then we can control its mating
そうすれば、その交配を制御できるようになります
easy to feed
餌を与えやすい
can reproduce in large numbers
大量に繁殖できる
that its body is small
体が小さいということ
We live in a small bottle
僕らは小さな瓶の中で生きている
You can raise two hundred
200 を集めることができます
So it takes up very little space
したがって、占有スペースは非常に小さくなります
that's basically cheap
それは基本的に安いです
And fruit flies I'll talk about later
ショウジョウバエについては後ほどお話します
it's been over a hundred months
百か月以上経ちました
years of research so there are very, very many
長年の研究の結果、非常に多くの研究結果が得られました。
resources for this research we have established a very good
この研究のための非常に優れたリソースを確立しました
Purebred strains, so-called purebred strains are
純血種、いわゆる純血種は、
Between one of its fruit camps and another fruit camp
フルーツ キャンプの 1 つと別のフルーツ キャンプの間
This change is very small, it is very different from people
この変化はとても小さなもので、人とは大きく異なります
Each person, this inheritance between two people
一人一人、二人の間のこの相続
Variations are very, very many
バリエーションはとてもたくさんあります
So this makes it an experiment
これは実験になります
It's a little simpler and then we also
もう少し簡単にして、私たちも
After many years of research across the field
分野全体で長年にわたる研究を経て
built many, many tools that allow us to manipulate
私たちが操作できるようにする非常に多くのツールを構築しました
So it has a lot of the convenience of these experiments above
したがって、上記の実験の多くの利便性を備えています
Then with these conditions, we can go to filter
次に、これらの条件を使用してフィルタリングに進みます。
The picture changes, let's talk about it later
画像の変更、これについては後で話しましょう
Then Tubian will find the gene of Tubian
そうすればトゥビアンはトゥビアンの遺伝子を見つけるだろう
Find this gene, it causes the result of this map change
この遺伝子を見つけてください、それがこのマップの変化の結果を引き起こします
We know that this gene is related to this function
この遺伝子がこの機能に関係していることがわかっています
So build it like this
それで、このように構築します
know that if the gene is mutated
遺伝子が突然変異しているかどうかを知る
it causes some kind of disease
それはある種の病気を引き起こす
then we can ask
それから私たちは尋ねることができます
Then why does this disease occur?
では、なぜこの病気が起こるのでしょうか？
Except for this gene
この遺伝子を除いて
What other genes are also involved
他にどのような遺伝子が関与しているのか
So in this way we will treat the disease
このようにして病気を治療します
Mechanism of healing
治癒のメカニズム
will have a more in-depth understanding
より深い理解が得られるでしょう
Once we know the mechanism
仕組みが分かれば
why do you get sick
なぜ病気になるのですか
Which genes are changed
どの遺伝子が変化するか
We can design some strategies to treat
治療のためのいくつかの戦略を立てることができます
you target a gene
あなたは遺伝子を標的にします
Design certain drugs against a certain protein
特定のタンパク質に対する特定の薬剤を設計する
or drug screening
または薬物スクリーニング
So this is what fruit flies can use in
これがショウジョウバエが利用できるものです
The human disease we're going to talk about today
今日お話しする人間の病気について
Use above
上面之用
then why fruit flies
ではなぜショウジョウバエが飛ぶのか
Just said it's cheap
安いって言っただけだよ
and it's fast
そして速いです
because you make a fruit fly
あなたがショウジョウバエを作るから
you're only two weeks old
あなたはまだ生後2週間です
12 days
12日間
We can easily do several generations of genetic experiments
数世代にわたる遺伝子実験を簡単に行うことができる
As long as you use a mouse, it will take a long time
マウスを使うと時間がかかる
As long as you use elephants, it will be even worse.
象を使う以上、さらに大変なことになる
So just do a few things quickly
だから、いくつかのことをすぐに実行してください
And after more than a hundred years of accumulation
そして百年以上の蓄積を経て
have a lot of knowledge
たくさんの知識を持っています
Presumably there isn't a single other multicellular organism
おそらく多細胞生物は他に一つも存在しない
we know so much
私たちはたくさんのことを知っています
Accumulated a lot of research resources
多くの研究リソースを蓄積
Another very important thing is
もう一つ非常に重要なことは、
The group of people who studied the fruit camp from the very beginning
フルーツキャンプを初期から研究してきた集団
It is the tradition established by the first big brother
初代兄貴が築いた伝統です
makes everyone think
みんなに考えさせられる
Resource information for all research
すべての研究に関するリソース情報
Should be to share is to share
共有すべきであることは共有することです
that this is very important
これはとても重要だということ
This is actually why I chose to do fruit camp back then
実はこれが当時私がフルーツキャンプをしようと思った理由です
Because at that time I wanted to say that I would go back to Taiwan in the future
その時私は将来台湾に戻ると言いたかったからです。
that was nearly 30 years ago
それは30年近く前のことです
we are very worried
私たちはとても心配しています
I am worried that if I return to Taiwan, I will be cut off from the world
台湾に戻ったら世界から切り離されてしまうのではないかと心配です
So as a fruit fly, I feel like I can get all this information
だからショウジョウバエとして、このすべての情報を得ることができるような気がする
I can get all the mutants from others
他人からすべてのミュータントを入手できる
Until now, the tradition of this community has been maintained like this.
現在までこのコミュニティの伝統はこのようにして維持されてきました。
The third important thing is that fruit flies are actually very similar to people
3番目に重要なことは、ショウジョウバエは実際には人間に非常に似ているということです
About 75% of these genes cause disease in humans
これらの遺伝子の約 75% が人間の病気を引き起こします。
We can find it all in fruit flies
ショウジョウバエですべてを見つけることができます
So fruit flies can be used to study human disease
ショウジョウバエは人間の病気の研究に使用できる
We'll talk more about this later
これについては後ほど詳しく説明します
One more thing I think is also very important is
もう一つ、私が非常に重要だと思うのは、
There are also single-celled organisms that are more convenient for us to study
私たちが研究するのに便利な単細胞生物もあります。
Siomyces bacterium
シオミセス属細菌
It's faster and cheaper for all the things just said
今言ったことすべてを考えると、そのほうが早くて安いです
But it's a little boring
でもちょっと退屈だよ
it is not a multicellular organism
それは多細胞生物ではありません
Look at a Xiaomai fungus, it is round like that
小梅菌を見てください、あんなに丸いんです
it looks boring
退屈そう
The various conditions it can have
さまざまな条件が考えられます
Also different from us
私たちとも違う
But what about fruit flies?
しかしショウジョウバエはどうでしょうか？
Even its nervous system is similar to ours
神経系も私たちと似ています
it has various behaviors
さまざまな動作があります
are very close to people
人々にとても近いです
so we can use it to study things that humans are interested in
人間が興味を持っていることを研究するためにそれを使うことができます
it's simple enough and complex enough
それは十分に単純であり、十分に複雑です
So the complexity is just right
したがって、複雑さはちょうどいいです
The study of the fruit fly began in 1910
ショウジョウバエの研究は 1910 年に始まりました
I just said fruit flies are everywhere
ショウジョウバエはどこにでもいると言いました
So in early labs it was very easy for you to have fruit flies coming in from outside
したがって、初期の研究室では、ショウジョウバエが外部から侵入するのは非常に簡単でした
Then just raise it and play it
あとは上げて演奏するだけです
Until 1910 this Thomas Hunt Morgan
1910年まではこのトーマス・ハント・モーガン
He is at Columbia University
彼はコロンビア大学にいます
Then he started to find a fruit fly
それから彼はショウジョウバエを探し始めました
Fruit flies normally have red eyes
ショウジョウバエは通常赤い目をしています
The one he found was white eyes
彼が見つけたのは白い目だった
And this white-eyed fruit fly he mated it
そしてこのメ​​ジロショウジョウバエと彼は交配した
I found out that white eyes are hereditary
白目は遺伝することが判明
And this white eye always follows the gender
そしてこの白い目は常に性別に従います
it only appears in males
それは男性にのみ現れます
So we know it's a recessive mutation
したがって、それが劣性突然変異であることがわかります
Then it's sex-linked
それなら性別も関係あるよ
It follows the sex chromosome X chromosome
性染色体 X 染色体に続きます
So from here it published a paper a paper
ここから論文を次々と発表しました
that proves the gene
それは遺伝子を証明する
This was originally an abstract concept
これはもともと抽象的な概念でした
gene it proves it's located on a chromosome
遺伝子はそれが染色体上にあることを証明する
Chromosomes are things we can see under a microscope
染色体は顕微鏡で見ることができるものです
So let's make this gene an entity
それでは、この遺伝子を実体にしてみましょう
Then you can do research and experiment
その後、研究や実験を行うことができます
So because of this study
ですから、この研究のおかげで
it won the nobel prize in 1933
1933年にノーベル賞を受賞しました
That early Drosophila research
初期のショウジョウバエの研究
Found that Drosophila has this giant chromosome
ショウジョウバエはこの巨大な染色体を持っていることが判明しました
It's just a chromosome its DNA replicates replicates replicates
それは単なる染色体であり、その DNA は複製され、複製されます。
But it doesn't separate, unlike our normal chromosomes that will separate after duplication
しかし、複製後に分離する通常の染色体とは異なり、分離しません。
it's all connected
すべてはつながっている
So it will replicate ten times. Two to the tenth power is a thousand times.
つまり、10 回複製されることになり、2 の 10 乗は 1,000 回になります。
A thousand chromosomes, a thousand pieces of DNA glued together
千の染色体、千の DNA が接着されている
so it becomes big
だから大きくなる
under the microscope when very large
非常に大きい場合は顕微鏡下で
At that time, only optical microscopes
当時は光学顕微鏡のみ
Under the microscope, you can see such a dark and light-colored
顕微鏡で見ると、このような濃い色と薄い色のものが見えます
This type of pattern is fixed
このタイプのパターンは固定です
Every cell in every fruit fly is the same
すべてのショウジョウバエのすべての細胞は同じです
so it can position it
位置決めできるように
Sometimes such chromosomes will appear
時々そのような染色体が現れることがあります
There will be a sweep in the middle
真ん中にスイープがあるだろう
Because you can see the shape of the chromosome, you will know which section to scan
染色体の形状が見えるので、どの部分をスキャンすればよいか分かります
what kind of mutation
どのような突然変異ですか
You know that gene is located in this section
遺伝子がこのセクションにあることがわかります
So utilize a tool like this
そこで、このようなツールを活用します
twenty or thirty years
二十年か三十年
just did a lot of work
たくさんの仕事をしました
Know the behavior of chromosomes
染色体の動きを知る
How chromosomes recombine
染色体がどのように組み換えられるか
How come something missing these
どうしてこれらが欠けているのでしょうか
How are the genes passed on?
遺伝子はどのように受け継がれるのでしょうか？
Then the location of the gene on the chromosome
次に、染色体上の遺伝子の位置
So about thirty years or so
それで30年くらいかな
just two things
たった2つのこと
is extremely important in genetics
遺伝学において非常に重要です
one is fruit camp
一つはフルーツキャンプ
one is corn
一つはトウモロコシです
one animal one plant
1 つの動物 1 つの植物
That's all because their chromosomes are special
それは彼らの染色体が特別だからです
So you can track chromosomal changes
染色体の変化を追跡できるようにするため
So this is Morgan
じゃあモーガンだよ
His Fly Group at Columbia University
コロンビア大学のフライグループ
very shabby one
とてもみすぼらしいもの
Bananas hanging on a laboratory wall
研究室の壁にぶら下がっているバナナ
Then there are glass jars with fruit flies
それからショウジョウバエの入ったガラス瓶があります
But such a laboratory
でもそんな研究室
Dominate modern genetics for about 30 years
約30年間にわたり現代遺伝学を支配する
Then there's Morgan
それからモーガンです
Then Muller et al.
次に、ミュラーら。
He also took the Norbell speech
彼はノーベルのスピーチにも参加した
Then the other two disciples of Morgan
それからモーガンの他の二人の弟子
Both Britjus and Sturdivus are masters of genetics
Britjus と Sturdivus はどちらも遺伝学の達人です
about 30 years
約30年
Genetics is fruit fly plus corn
遺伝学はショウジョウバエとトウモロコシです
That Morgan's students include this one
モーガンの生徒にはこの人も含まれていること
Herman Muller
ハーマン・ミュラー
He also made a lot of contributions
彼も多大な貢献をしてくれました
The most important thing is
最も重要なことは
He discovered that taking fruit flies and taking them to X-rays
彼はショウジョウバエを捕まえてレントゲン検査に連れて行くと、
will produce a mutation
突然変異を起こすだろう
X-rays break chromosomes
X線は染色体を破壊する
genetic changes
遺伝子の変化
So this one is
それで、これは
is to tell us that radiation can damage our DNA
それは、放射線が私たちのDNAに損傷を与える可能性があることを教えてくれます。
will cause mutation
突然変異を引き起こすだろう
Well, this was way before the atomic age.
まあ、これは原子時代よりずっと前のことです。
But later it affected our consideration of this radiation.
しかしその後、それはこの放射線に関する私たちの考察に影響を与えました。
The other is that you can artificially take X-rays
もう一つは、人工的にX線を撮影できることです。
Later, I switched to taking some drugs to produce mutations
その後、突然変異を引き起こすいくつかの薬の服用に切り替えました
Mutation can be done for research
研究のために突然変異を行うこともできる
why is this important
何でこれが大切ですか
Because Morgan when he found that one mutation
モーガンがその突然変異を見つけたとき
It just fell from the sky
まさに空から落ちてきた
the chances of that are very very low
可能性は非常に低いです
then you take your luck doing research
それなら研究するのは運次第だ
But once you can artificially promote mutations
しかし、人為的に突然変異を促進できるようになると、
You have a much higher chance of getting the mutation
突然変異を起こす可能性がはるかに高くなります
So it becomes very convenient
とても便利になります
But the good times don't last long
しかし、良い時間は長くは続かない
it's the same tool
それは同じツールです
If you ask these questions to a certain level, you will not be able to continue asking them.
これらの質問をある程度のレベルまで尋ねると、質問を続けることができなくなります。
all done
すべて完了
So to 1940 5060
1940 5060 まで
Drosophila becomes obsolete
ショウジョウバエは死滅する
has fallen to such an extent that almost no one is doing fruit flies anymore.
ショウジョウバエをやっている人はほとんどいないほどに減少しました。
Bacteria and viruses were the most popular at that time
当時最も人気があったのは細菌とウイルスでした
Do these genetic studies faster
これらの遺伝子研究をより迅速に行う
So a lot of people put in
なのでたくさんの人が入れてます
that ushered in a new era
新しい時代の到来を告げた
Fruit flies are eliminated
ショウジョウバエは駆除されます
It was 1970
1970年のことでした
Only then did someone apply these new molecular biology techniques
そのときになって初めて、誰かがこれらの新しい分子生物学技術を応用しました。
brought it back and used it on fruit flies
持ち帰ってショウジョウバエに使用しました
Because fruit flies have a very good knowledge in the past
ショウジョウバエは過去に非常に優れた知識を持っているため、
So he introduced this new technology
そこで彼はこの新しいテクノロジーを導入しました
As a result, a lot of previous
その結果、これまでの多くの
It is important to know that there is no way to study these issues
これらの問題を研究する方法はないことを知っておくことが重要です
Take it back for research
研究のために持ち帰ってください
The second golden age of the fruit fly
ショウジョウバエの第二黄金期
until now
今まで
I should have said a moment ago
と言うべきだった
this chromosome
この染色体
When I was in college, I told Wang Feichang
大学時代、私は王飛昌さんにこう言いました。
I study botany
私は植物学を勉強しています
we'll have genetics
私たちには遺伝学があるでしょう
Geneticists did genetic experiments
遺伝学者は遺伝子実験を行った
raising fruit flies
養果蠅
and look at this giant chromosome under a microscope
そしてこの巨大な染色体を顕微鏡で見てみましょう
That fruit fly raised
あのショウジョウバエが発生した
That food smells bad after fermentation
その食べ物は発酵すると臭くなる
we have to wash the bottles
私たちはボトルを洗わなければなりません
Stinks
臭い
I swore I would never touch a fruit fly again.
私は二度とショウジョウバエには触れないと誓った。
Then look at this microscope
じゃあこの顕微鏡を見てください
i get dizzy
めまいがする
because of the quick movement
動きが素早いので
will be dizzy
めまいがするだろう
I also swore never to touch a microscope again.
私も二度と顕微鏡には触らないと誓った。
It's too early to say
言うには時期尚早です
As a result, later
その結果、後々、
will do it for decades
何十年もやるだろう
Ok so I'm back to this fruit fly picture
さて、このショウジョウバエの写真に戻ります
here are some
ここにあるいくつかの
these funny pictures
これらの面白い写真
This is Wild Type
これは野生型です
that's what we call normal
それが私たちが普通と呼ぶものです
red eyes with wings
翼のある赤い目
then have six legs
それなら足が6本あるよ
This is the first Baiyan Guoying I found
初めて見つけた白岩国英です
The pigment in his eyes is gone
彼の目の色素は消えてしまった
Then the same gene can have different forms of pictures
すると同じ遺伝子でも異なる形の絵を持つことができる
This one is called White Apricot
こちらはホワイトアプリコットというそうです
his eyes are not so red
彼の目はそれほど赤くない
Pigment becomes lighter
色素が軽くなる
Still a picture of the same gene
まだ同じ遺伝子の写真
This fruit shadow with its wings rolled up is called Curly
羽根を巻き上げたこのフルーツの影は カーリーと呼ばれます
This one has his body turned into Yellow
こちらは体が黄色くなっています
from black to yellow
黒から黄色へ
It's also a matter of pigment
色素の問題でもあります
This one will be mentioned later
これについては後述します
Called Illus and he has no eyes
イルスと呼ばれ、彼には目がありません
He's all right, but his eyes are missing.
彼は大丈夫ですが、目が欠けています。
So earlier studies did a lot of this
したがって、以前の研究ではこれの多くが行われていました
image above form
フォーム上の画像
We know that such mutations are related to development
このような突然変異が発達に関連していることがわかっています
What about some other mutations?
他の突然変異についてはどうですか?
he died
彼は死んだ
Mutation occurs and he dies
突然変異が起きて死ぬ
What can you do when you die?
死んだら何ができるの？
You told me that this gene is very important
この遺伝子はとても重要だと私に言いました
so without him
だから彼なしでは
what else to do
他に何をすべきか
Someone used it to study his death
誰かが彼の死を研究するためにそれを使用した
when did he die
いついなくなった
What happens to your body when you die?
死ぬとあなたの体はどうなりますか？
You know he can develop to this stage
彼がこの段階まで成長できることを知っています
Indicates that the gene is at this stage
遺伝子がこの段階にあることを示します
before is not important
前は重要ではない
Then at this stage it is important
そして、この段階で重要なのは
so he can't go on
だから彼は続けられない
so you can know a lot
それでたくさんのことを知ることができます
Then you can also design various
そうすると、いろいろなデザインもできるようになります
Interesting way to screen for mutations
突然変異をスクリーニングする興味深い方法
For example, someone did a screening
たとえば、誰かがスクリーニングを行いました。
Because he really can fly
彼は本当に空を飛べるから
He put Guoruo in a cage
彼はグオルオを檻に入れました
Same network power
同網通電
then go knock
それからノックに行きます
Those who can fly will fly up and hit the Internet
飛べる者は飛んでインターネットに飛び込むだろう
electrocuted
感電死した
the flightless fruit camp
飛べないフルーツキャンプ
just survive
就活下來
that won't fly
それは飛ばないでしょう
you can imagine it has several possibilities
いくつかの可能性があることは想像できます
one is that it may not have wings
一つは翼がないかもしれないということ
so you can study wing development
翼の発達を学ぶことができます
one is that it has wings
一つは翼があること
but it can't fly
でも飛べない
won't fly it may be because
飛ばないのはそのせいかもしれない
Problems with the muscles that control flight
飛行を制御する筋肉の問題
Or a problem with the nerves that control the flight
またはハエを制御する神経の問題
Or a problem with the control of the brain
それとも脳の制御に問題があるのか
So it can be divided into many more
なので、さらにたくさんに分けることができます
So the same filter
つまり同じフィルター
you can find a variety of these mutations
これらのさまざまな突然変異を見つけることができます
So how to design this screening mutation
では、このスクリーニング変異はどのように設計するのでしょうか?
it's a very interesting place
とても興味深い場所です
Then as the years passed, we continued to
それから年月が経っても、私たちは続けました。
There are several important techniques
重要なテクニックがいくつかあります
Then we can put the genes back in the fruit camp.
そうすれば、遺伝子をフルーツキャンプに戻すことができます。
we can do whatever we want
私たちはやりたいことは何でもできます
want to control this gene
この遺伝子をコントロールしたい
let it show where
どこにあるかを示させてください
what time to show
何時に見せますか
We can be inside a fruit eagle individual
私たちはオオワシの個体の中にいることができる
Let some of its cells be damaged
細胞の一部を損傷させる
some cells are good
一部の細胞は良好です
So making this genetic fit
したがって、この遺伝子を適合させるには
Now we have new technology
今、私たちは新しい技術を持っています
let us do whatever we want
やりたいことは何でもしましょう
you don't rely on mutations
突然変異に頼らない
just happen naturally
ただ自然に起こるだけ
But I just want to change this one gene
でも私はただこの遺伝子を変えたいだけなの
I change it like an engineer
エンジニアのように変えていきます
So for Guoying
だから郭英にとっては
Now we can pretty much do whatever we want
今では、やりたいことはほとんど何でもできるようになりました
in any particular cell
任意のセル内で
specific time
特定的時間
we can have a way to change
私たちには変える方法がある
A certain gene its expression or its function
ある遺伝子の発現または機能
The precision of such manipulation
このような操作の正確さ
Can also be done in other creatures
他の生き物でもできる
But the precision is far less than
しかし、精度ははるかに劣ります
here
ここ
We can do the same in mice
マウスでも同じことができます
Of course it is much more expensive and much slower
もちろん、はるかに高価で、はるかに時間がかかります
But the precision of manipulation
しかし操作の精度は
far inferior to fruit eagle
フルーツイーグルにははるかに劣ります
Fruit eagle has many benefits
フルーツイーグルには多くの利点があります
Its genome was sequenced in 2000
そのゲノムは 2000 年に解読されました。
this ordered paper
この配列された紙
There are so many authors working together
たくさんの作家さんが協力してくださっています
Not just the genetic sequencing of a fruit eagle
オオワシの遺伝子配列を解析するだけではない
Also did 12 different sequences
12の異なるシーケンスも実行しました
the total can be compared
合計を比較できる
If we take two total DNA sequences and compare
2 つの合計 DNA 配列を取得して比較すると、
what they have in common
彼らの共通点は何ですか
may be more important in evolution
進化においてはもっと重要かもしれない
so will be kept
それで保管されます
they will change
彼らは変わるだろう
Probably something less important
おそらくそれほど重要ではない何か
So this allows us to quickly
これにより、すぐに
to focus on the important parts
重要な部分に集中するために
I'll talk about it again
それについてはまた話します
this development
この展開
Drosophila begins with a fertilized egg
ショウジョウバエは受精卵から始まります
just a cell
ただの細胞
This cell divides many times
この細胞は何度も分裂します
after the split
分割後
It's going to look like this when it's an embryo
胎芽のときはこんな感じになります
You can see that this already has some body segments
これにはすでにいくつかのボディセグメントがあることがわかります
it is divided into many body segments
多くの体の部分に分かれています
That's a total of fourteen verses
合計14節です
The basic structure of an insect is the head
昆虫の基本構造は頭です
boobs then belly
おっぱい、次に腹
The three parts of the head, chest and abdomen
頭、胸、腹部の３つの部位
what about the chest
胸はどうですか
Always three quarters
いつも4分の3
This is SORAC
ソラックです
So T1 T2 T3
だから T1 T2 T3
Each of the three sections grows a pair of legs
3 つのセクションのそれぞれに、一対の脚が生えています。
Then the second section grows a wing
次に、2番目のセクションに翼が生えます
In the third section, a small wing will grow
第三セクションでは小さな翼が生えます
called a balance bar
バランスバーと呼ばれる
That abdomen has A1 to A8
あのお腹にはA1からA8まである
eight knots
八節
That
それか
Abdomen no longer have legs
腹部には足がなくなりました
that such a heavy body structure
こんなに重い体の構造とは
Actually
実際
Black Fetus, Late and Larval Stages
黒い胎児、後期および幼虫段階
can already see
すでに見えています
so it's in a short time
だから短時間で
somites
体節
Let me show you one
一つお見せしましょう
Movie
映画
Um
えーっと
I just tried it and it still works
試してみましたが、まだ機能します
ok then
わかりました、それでは
No way, I was going to show you this one
まさか、これを見せるつもりだったんだ
early developmental process
初期の発達過程
that same
それと同じ
You can tell it has these segments
これらのセグメントがあることがわかります
someone made one
誰かが作った
screening mutations
突然変異のスクリーニング
and it finds this with all sorts of mutations
あらゆる種類の突然変異でこれが見つかります
This dying embryo
この瀕死の胎児
dead in embryo
胎児の状態で死んでいる
like this one
このように
just compare with normal
ノーマルと比べてみてください
it's like the body
それは体のようなものです
this colored piece
この色の部分
all gone
全部なくなった
so is this
これもそうです
All these colored parts are gone
色のついた部分が全部なくなってしまった
gone here too
ここにも行った
So from the analysis of these mutant species
したがって、これらの突然変異種の分析から
The order in which they discovered
発見した順番
A very important structure like this comes out
このような非常に重要な構造が出てきます
That is, the embryo must first determine the head and tail from the early stage
つまり、胚は初期段階から頭と尾を決定する必要があります。
Then through a series of genes
その後、一連の遺伝子を通じて
Divide this embryo step by step into 14 somites
この胚を段階的に 14 体節に分割します
that part is very important
その部分はとても重要です
But it's complicated
でも複雑です
easy to bring
簡単に持ち運べる
Such research won a Nobel Prize
このような研究はノーベル賞を受賞しました
After it is divided into 14 body segments
その後、体を14の部分に分けます
grow into a mature individual
成熟した個人に成長する
Each body segment has a different structure
体の各部分は異なる構造を持っています
I just talked about this T2
この T2 について話したばかりです
The second section of the chest will grow wings like this
胸の2番目のセクションにはこのように翼が生えます
What about the third part of the chest?
胸の3番目の部分はどうでしょうか？
Such a small balance bar
こんなに小さなバランスバー
Nothing grows in the first section of the chest
胸の最初の部分には何も成長しません
have a mutation in a gene
遺伝子に突然変異がある
This gene is called UBX
この遺伝子はUBXと呼ばれます
Just let this T3
このT3をそのままにしておきます
The third section grows exactly like the second section
3 番目のセクションは 2 番目のセクションとまったく同じように成長します
So what about a fruit fly?
ではショウジョウバエはどうでしょうか？
Now there are two T2
これで T2 は 2 つになりました
there are two pairs of wings
二対の翼があります
that's very interesting
それはとても興味深いですね
except this one looks like a monster
ただ、これはモンスターのように見えます
very interesting
とても興味深い
The change creates a difference between the two body segments
この変更により、2 つの体のセグメント間に違いが生じます
However, the two body segments are quite different in shape.
ただし、2 つの体の部分の形状はまったく異なります。
So a genetic shift changes the past
つまり遺伝子の変化が過去を変える
another one
もう一つ
This is Guoying's head and this side is the secondary eye
これがGuoyingの頭で、こちら側が副目です。
this is the mouth
これが口です
and here are its tentacles
そしてこれがその触手です
antennum
アンテナ
Here's another mutation
ここに別の突然変異があります
It makes this tentacles completely into feet
この触手は完全に足になります
This is a very complete leg
非常に完成度の高い脚です
The legs are divided into many knots
足はたくさんの結び目に分かれています
So this one mutation is called antennanum pedia
したがって、この 1 つの突然変異は触角ペディアと呼ばれます
pedia is feet
ペディアは足です
Same it a gene change
それも遺伝子の変化です
Make the original two forms above
上記の 2 つのフォームを元に作成します
very different structures
非常に異なる構造
One tentacles and one foot transforms
1 本の触手と 1 つの足が変形します
say these two
この二人を言う
The difference in the two body structures is only in the
2 つの体の構造の違いは、
a gene
遺伝子
So this gene controls
つまり、この遺伝子が制御しているのです
the development of a part of the body
体の一部の発達
The part of the embryo mentioned earlier
先ほど述べた胚の部分
these two did it
この二人がやった
And then the double-breasted fruit camp behind this
そしてこの後ろにあるダブルブレストフルーツキャンプ
This Al-Louis did it
このアル・ルイがやったんだ
The three won the Nobel Prize together in 1995
3人は1995年に一緒にノーベル賞を受賞した
Then you say OK this
それからあなたは「これでOK」と言う
You found the gene that controls fruit wing development
果実の翅の発達を制御する遺伝子を発見しました
So what's so great
それで何がそんなに素晴らしいのか
Right, man has no wings
そう、人間には翼がないのです
What about in the fruit camp?
フルーツキャンプではどうでしょうか？
find a gene at the beginning
先頭の遺伝子を見つける
It was later discovered that there is actually a series of such genes
実際にそのような遺伝子が一連に存在することが後に判明しました。
that and this set of genes is interesting
あれとこの遺伝子セットは興味深い
the order in which it is arranged on the chromosome
染色体上での並び順
is consistent with the order in which they affect body parts
身体部分に影響を与える順序と一致している
This one affects the development of the first tone
これは最初の音の展開に影響します
Then this will affect the development of the tail
そうなると尾の発育に影響が出てしまいます
come in order
順番に来てください
Then such things exist in fruit flies
ショウジョウバエにもこのようなものが存在する
It is more interesting to find
見つけたほうが面白いよ
It's not just fruit flies
ショウジョウバエだけではない
Assuming only fruit flies exist, I won't talk about it today
ショウジョウバエだけが存在すると仮定して、今日はそれについては話しません
Then it's because in mice and in people
それはマウスでも人間でもそうなるからです
in various creatures
いろいろな生き物の中で
have these genes
これらの遺伝子を持っています
There is a group of fruit flies
ショウジョウバエの群れがいます
In humans or mice there are four groups of these genes
ヒトまたはマウスには、これらの遺伝子の 4 つのグループがあります。
Then they basically correspond like this
その後、基本的にこのように対応します
So basically if there are fruit flies, there are people too.
つまり基本的にショウジョウバエがいれば人間もいるということです。
It's just that people are a little more complicated, a little more
ただ人間はもう少し複雑です、もう少し
Even more interesting is the order in which they are arranged
さらに興味深いのは、それらが配置されている順序です
It's roughly the same order as the fruit fly
ショウジョウバエとほぼ同じ順番です
So it means that the order must be important
ということは順番が大事ということですね
So why does this order matter until now?
では、なぜ今までこの順序が重要だったのでしょうか?
Why is it left behind in evolution
なぜ進化に取り残されるのか
Not very clear
あまり明確ではありません
Diverse
多様
Then such a gene affects development in Drosophila
そして、そのような遺伝子はショウジョウバエの発生に影響を与える
Are there any rats?
そこのネズミの中で
Then we see these genes
次に、これらの遺伝子がわかります
Indicated here in different colors
ここでは異なる色で示されています
where they appear on the body
体のどこに現れるか
that will affect
それは影響するだろう
I just saw that fruit flies are body segments
ショウジョウバエは体の一部であることを今見ました
segmental passage
分節一節
So what kind of segmented structure do we humans have?
では、私たち人間はどのような分節構造を持っているのでしょうか？
The most obvious is our spine
最もわかりやすいのは背骨です
The spine is divided into cervical, thoracic, lumbar, shoulder, and coccyx
脊椎は頸椎、胸椎、腰椎、肩、尾骨に分かれています
Every single one of these spines you take out to see
あなたが取り出して見るこれらの背骨の一つ一つ
its shape is different
その形は違います
Especially the part of the thoracic spine
特に胸椎の部分
I still need to grow this rib
この肋骨をまだ成長させなければなりません
The different genes are called Hox genes
さまざまな遺伝子は Hox 遺伝子と呼ばれます
it manifests itself in this
それはこの中に現れています
Different positions of the body from front to back
前と後ろで体の位置が違う
that this is different
これは違うということ
It determines where you grew up
それはあなたがどこで育ったのかを決定します
what kind of vertebra
どのような椎骨ですか
we watch mice
私たちはネズミを観察します
This cervical vertebra of the mouse is here
このネズミの頸椎はここにあります
There are seven vertebrae
椎骨は7つあります
What about chickens? There are so many cervical vertebrae.
鶏はどうでしょうか? 頸椎は非常にたくさんあります。
about a dozen sections
十数のセクション
Then he has less thoracic spine
それから彼は胸椎が少ないです
And this mouse has more thoracic vertebrae
そうすると、このマウスには胸椎がたくさんあります
The demarcation points of these cervical and thoracic vertebrae
これらの頸椎と胸椎の境界点
These are the Hawks genes just mentioned
これらは今言及したホークスの遺伝子です
expressive boundaries
表現力豊かな境界線
So these boundaries the range they represent
したがって、これらの境界はパフォーマンスに幅があります
It determines what kind of bone will grow in this position
この位置でどのような種類の骨が成長するかが決まります
Another place is
もう一つの場所は、
This is also Hawks content
こちらもホークスの内容です
13 or 11
13 または 11
Then if under normal conditions
その後、通常の状態であれば
This is the metacarpal bone of a mouse
これはマウスの中手骨です
dye here
ここで染める
This red is dyed cartilage
この赤は軟骨を染めたものです
blue stained bones
青く染まった骨
If this gene is broken
この遺伝子が壊れると
Its development is slightly different
その展開は少し異なります
If both genes are broken
両方の遺伝子が壊れた場合
it becomes like this
このようになります
It just doesn't grow the bones at the far end.
遠端の骨が成長しないだけです。
Mutation of another gene on mating
交配時の別の遺伝子の突然変異
This is another one called Glycery
こちらもグリセリーと呼ばれるものです
If there is something wrong with this gene
この遺伝子に何か異常があると
look at this time
この時間を見てください
fingers become more than five
指が5本以上になる
it has about seven to eight here
ここには7つか8つくらいあります
Then if both genes are completely destroyed
そして、両方の遺伝子が完全に破壊されると、
it has thirteen fingers
指が13本ある
And it's not as long as the front
そして前ほど長くない
None of the remote
リモコンはどれもありません
So these genes affect the development of many different parts of our body
したがって、これらの遺伝子は私たちの体のさまざまな部分の発達に影響を与えます
Let me talk about the eyes again
もう一度目の話をさせてください
Then the facts of my own experiments study this eye
そして、私自身の実験的事実がこの目を研究します
This is restudy
これは再勉強です
very beautiful very regular
とても美しい とても普通
This was filmed with a wire
ワイヤーで撮影したものです
This is an optical microscope
これは光学顕微鏡です
Taken by Jiebo Microscope
Jiebo 顕微鏡で撮影
normal it is red
普通は赤いです
this one is a mutant it's white
これはミュータントです、白です
Because the arrangement of this eye is very regular
この目の配置はとても規則正しいので
so any small change
だからどんな小さな変化でも
you can easily detect
簡単に検出できます
So this is a
これは
you see this and you think
これを見てあなたはこう思います
the surface is very rough
粗い表面
irregular
不規則な
This is also a mutation
これも突然変異です
This is another mutation
これもまた突然変異です
The whole eye is gone
目全体が消えてしまった
Then there is another mutation
それからまた突然変異が起こる
his eyes got small
彼の目は小さくなった
and small he is
そして彼は小さいです
from top to bottom like this
このように上から下まで
Straight
真っ直ぐ
So just look at the type
なので、種類だけからすると
we can see
見える
Various can affect the eyes
さまざまなことが目に影響を与える可能性があります
developmental mutations
発達上の突然変異
Then you can do it from here
それならここからやってもいいよ
a lot of analysis
たくさんの分析
I think the funniest thing is
それから、私が最も興味深いと思うのは、
this one mutation
この突然変異
just said Eilus
ちょうどエイラスが言った
Then he mutated and the whole eye disappeared.
その後、彼は突然変異を起こし、目全体が消えてしまいました。
So this means
つまり、これは意味します
This gene is
この遺伝子は、
Necessary for secondary actor development
二次アクターの開発に必要
If his eyes are broken, they won't grow back
彼の目は壊れたら元には戻らない
that's more interesting
それはもっと面白いです
If this gene
この遺伝子なら
bring him to show on the wings
彼を連れて翼の上に見せてください
or on the head
または頭の上に
he can be on the wings
彼は翼の上に立つことができる
on the legs
足の上に
On the legs, and then on this antennae, there are eyes
足の上、そしてこの触覚の上に目がある
So without him, the eyes can't grow
だから彼なしでは目は成長できない
Then you show him in that place
それからあなたは彼にその場所を見せます
Just grow an eye
ただ目を育てるだけ
So this gene determines
したがって、この遺伝子が決定します
Do you want to develop into eyes?
目に発症するかどうかが問題
decide his fate
彼の運命を決める
Then this experiment is a Swiss
そうすると、この実験はスイス人です
A Water Garing made in his laboratory
彼の研究室で作られたウォーターガリング
Then you see the eyes are very beautiful
そうしたら、目がとても美しいのがわかります
Then the same if this gene directly affects the effect
この遺伝子が効果に直接影響する場合も同様です
i won't talk here
ここでは話しません
The same gene exists in both mice and humans
マウスと人間には同じ遺伝子が存在する
In mice, this gene mutation is called small eyes.
マウスでは、この遺伝子変異は小さな目と呼ばれます。
His eyes became smaller
彼の目は小さくなった
this is normal
これは正常です
What about human genes?
人間の遺伝子はどうなるのでしょうか？
He doesn't have red membranes in his eyes
彼の目には赤い膜がありません
The man, the mouse and the fly, this gene
人間、ネズミ、ハエ、この遺伝子
are very similar in structure
構造が非常に似ています
So if this gene
つまり、この遺伝子が
It controls the development of the eyes
目の発達をコントロールする
Some people say that this is called a master gene
これをマスター遺伝子と呼ぶ人もいる
it is master
それはマスターです
Then he decides whether the eyes should develop or not
それから目を発達させるかどうかを決定します
That other study said
他の研究ではこう言われています
It takes about 2,500 genes to make an eye
目を作るには約2,500個の遺伝子が必要
There is a very complicated process
非常に複雑なプロセスがあります
So we can imagine saying
したがって、次のように言うことが想像できます。
This I-LUS this gene
この I-LUS この遺伝子
it is a switch
それはスイッチです
it turns on the whole
それは全体的にオンになります
a program of reenactment of development
開発の再現プログラム
a program
一個program
Well, someone did an experiment like this
さて、こんな実験をした人がいます
he put human genes
彼は人間の遺伝子を入れた
I just said that it is very similar to the genes of fruit flies
ショウジョウバエの遺伝子に非常に似ていると言いました。
It is used in fruit ants to express
果物のアリで表現するために使用されます。
Do exactly the same experiment as the fruit ants.
フルーツアリと全く同じ実験をしてみましょう。
what do you think will happen
何が起こると思いますか
it turns out
それが判明
Human genes are put in
人間の遺伝子が組み込まれている
put it in fruit ants
フルーツアリに入れます
can still produce an eye
まだ目を生成できます
So the resulting eyes are the eyes of fruit ants
結果として得られる目はフルーツアリの目です
or human eyes
または人間の目
What we put in is this switch
私たちが入れたのはこのスイッチです
it opens the city behind
それは後ろの街を開く
The whole city is still a city of fruit ants
街全体がまだフルーツアリの街
So it grows out as the secondary eye of fruit ants
果実アリの第二の目として成長します
This is very interesting, it means
これはとても興味深いですね、つまり、
It's been so long since evolution
進化から時間が経ちました
The original switch is still in use
オリジナルのスイッチはまだ使用されています
Obviously this switch is very important, it cannot be changed randomly
明らかに、このスイッチは非常に重要であり、ランダムに変更することはできません。
So from fruit flies to people
ショウジョウバエから人間まで
Someone pushes it further to simpler organisms
誰かがそれをさらに単純な生物に推し進めた
This gene was also found
こんな遺伝子も見つかった
Some even push it all the way to single-celled organisms
単細胞生物にまでそれを推し進める人もいます
we won't talk about that
それについては話しません
Anyway, there's a gene that matters
とにかく、重要な遺伝子があります
Then as long as you let this gene express
この遺伝子を発現させておく限り
it makes an eye
それは目を作ります
That power is a bit too much
その力はちょっと強すぎる
In case it accidentally behaves wrong
誤って動作を誤った場合に備えて
expressed in a cell
細胞内で発現する
That one cell becomes the eye
その一個の細胞が目になる
then we should
それなら私たちはすべきです
Inexplicably, there are some places with eyes
不可解ですが目が付いている箇所がいくつかあります
but it didn't happen
しかしそれは起こらなかった
So our laboratory has done such an experiment
そこで私たちの研究室ではこんな実験をしてみました
is that we found such a gene
私たちがそのような遺伝子を見つけたということです
It actually manifests in the embryo
それは実際には胎児に現れます
The location is not just where the eyes are
場所は目の届く場所だけではありません
it behaves elsewhere
それは他の場所で動作します
Apparently in those places it doesn't cause eyes
どうやらそれらの場所では目を引き起こすことはありません
So it's not that it's that powerful
だからと言ってそこまで強いわけではなく、
In addition we can also in this
さらに、これでもできます
On this tissue that will develop into wings in the future
将来羽になるこの組織に
performance, for example, in such a circle
たとえば、そのようなサークルでのパフォーマンス
It is only at this point that the cells of the eye are produced
この時点でのみ目の細胞が生成されます。
So it doesn't spawn eyes everywhere
どこにでも目が出現するわけではないので、
Then such research can be said later
そうすると、そのような研究は後から言えます。
Then it must cooperate with other factors.
次に、他の要素と連携する必要があります。
The one it wants to cooperate with only appears in this place
協力したいのはここにしか現れない
So it's only in that place that it can produce eyes
だからそこにしか目は生まれないんだよ
So this follow-up
そこで今回の続報は
did a series of studies like this
このような一連の研究を行いました
one of his collaborators
彼の協力者の一人
It was our lab that found this gene called Igon
Igonと呼ばれるこの遺伝子を発見したのは私たちの研究室でした
As the name suggests, this gene is also broken.
名前が示すように、この遺伝子も壊れています。
The eyes are gone, just gone
目は消えてしまった、ただ消えてしまっただけだ
So he is very similar to Iless
だから彼はアイレスにとても似ています
Let's find out his genes
彼の遺伝子を調べてみましょう
It is found that the structure is also very similar
構造もよく似ていることがわかります
But the two do different things
でも二人はやってることが違う
Express the Iless gene in places other than the eyes
Iless遺伝子を目以外の場所で発現させる
he will have eyes
彼には目があるだろう
But expressing the Igon gene in the body
しかし、体内でIgon遺伝子を発現させると、
He is still only next to the eyes
彼はまだ目の前にだけいる
can produce eyes
目を作り出すことができる
But it doesn't work anywhere other than the eyes
でも目以外は効かない
So he doesn't decide the fate of the eyes
だから彼が目の運命を決めるわけではない
This one decides the fate of the eyes
これが目の運命を決める
But we want to add the two together
しかし、私たちはその 2 つを足し合わせたいのです
I saw that every extra eye grew very big at this time
このとき、余分な目がすべてとても大きくなったのがわかりました
Then our experiments found that
その後、私たちの実験で次のことが分かりました。
It turns out that the Eros gene controls developmental destiny
エロス遺伝子が発達運命を制御していることが判明
Naegon, the gene that controls cell division
細胞分裂を制御する遺伝子「ネゴン」
So if you want to generate eyes in this place
この場所に目を生成したい場合は
It has very few cells, so it grows very small
細胞の数が非常に少ないので、非常に小さく成長します
But adding this one can increase the number of compound eye cells
でもこれを加えると複眼細胞の数を増やすことができる
so the eyes get bigger
それで目が大きくなる
So normally both genes need
したがって、通常は両方の遺伝子が必要です
to produce a true compound eye
本当の複眼を生み出すために
From these studies of the eyes, we can also see
これらの目に関する研究から、次のことがわかります。
There are various mutations that affect eye size
目の大きさに影響を与えるさまざまな変異が存在する
The normal eyes here just now are so big
さっきの普通の目がすごく大きい
Some mutations make the eyes smaller
いくつかの突然変異により目が小さくなる
more serious eye disappears
より深刻な目が消えます
So this is to make the eyes smaller
これは目を小さくするためです
There is another direction to make the eyes bigger
目を大きくするには別の方向があります
At this time, the eyes become a little swollen
この時、目が少し腫れます
That's more serious and it becomes like this
もっと深刻だとこうなる
so it wrinkled
だからしわが寄った
because it has too many cells
細胞が多すぎるから
Then you can't become such a big
そうしたらあんなに大きくなれないよ
so it folds up
それで折りたたまれます
So that's a lot like cancer
それは癌によく似ています
grow a tumor
腫瘍を成長させる
So some people use fruit flies to study cancer
ガンの研究にショウジョウバエを使う人もいます
Some people say that cancer has been studied for decades
がんは何十年も研究されてきたと言う人もいます
So now you join in the research with fruit flies.
さて、あなたもショウジョウバエの研究に参加しましょう。
Any chance of finding something new?
新しいものを見つけるチャンスはありますか？
it did find
それは見つけました
that's normal
それは正常です
This is a mutation found
これは突然変異が見つかったものです
it overproliferates this cell
それはこの細胞を過剰増殖させます
The growth area is very large
成長領域は非常に広い
so wrinkled like this
こんなにシワだらけ
This wrinkled look is a bit like a Shar Pei
このシワシワな見た目はちょっとシャーペイっぽいですね
basically an increase in surface area
基本的に表面積の増加
your body hasn't changed
あなたの体は変わっていない
So it just has to fold the skin
つまり、スキンを折りたたむだけで済みました
Shar Pei
シャーペイ
So this gene was originally called
したがって、この遺伝子はもともとこう呼ばれていました
Shopey Sharpei
ショピー・シャーペイ
Later, it was named earlier because of another person.
その後、別の人の名前により、以前に名前が付けられました。
So it's called Sovodor
だからソボドルって言うんです
This series of genes
この一連の遺伝子は、
Then I found out how they work
それから私はそれらがどのように機能するかを学びました
transmission of such a signal
そのような信号の送信
from cell surface
細胞表面から
And then all the way to the cell river
そしてセル川までずっと
control gene expression
遺伝子発現を制御する
such a signaling chain
このような信号伝達チェーン
hyperactivation
過活動
will produce such a situation
そのような状況を生み出します
it's a normal
それは普通です
A piece of tissue will develop into a wing in the future
組織の一部が将来翼に成長する
If this HIPPO is excessive, it will become like this
このHIPPOが過剰になるとこうなります
grow very big
とても大きく成長する
Such a PASSWARE was first found in Drosophila
このようなパスワードはショウジョウバエで最初に発見されました
Then it was discovered that in the rat people there are
その後、ラットマンが
In experiments with mice
マウスを使った実験では
If you overactivate this PASSWARE
このパスウェアを有効化しすぎた場合
The whole liver becomes so big
肝臓全体がとても大きくなります
Then in this signal transmission chain
そして、この信号伝達チェーンでは
There is a gene that is Selvador, Sarpy mentioned here
ここで言及されているセルバドール、サーピーという遺伝子があります。
Another gene is called HIPPO
もう一つの遺伝子はHIPPOと呼ばれます
that's what makes this organization big
それがこの組織を大きくする理由です
just like homer
ホーマーみたいに
So this HIPPO PASSWARE was the first to be found in fruit flies
つまり、この HIPPO PASSWARE はショウジョウバエで最初に発見されたものでした
In the past in human cancer research
過去には人間のがん研究において
did not find this one
これは見つかりませんでした
Then this password is very important
このパスワードは非常に重要です
Because cancer takes a tumor to grow
がんは腫瘍が成長するのに時間がかかるため、
He wants cell division
彼は細胞分裂を望んでいます
he will grow a lot
彼は大きく成長するだろう
Then our body has some mechanism
そして、私たちの体には何らかのメカニズムがあり、
you split too much
分けすぎだよ
i'm going to kill you
あなたを殺すつもりだ
So the cell kills itself
つまり細胞は自ら死滅する
After such a password is activated
このようなパスワードが有効になった後
On the one hand, he makes the cells divide more
一方で、彼は細胞をさらに分裂させます
On the one hand, keep him from dying
一方で、彼を死なせないでください
So the one who was supposed to die didn't die
だから死ぬはずの人は死ななかった
So many and not dead
たくさんいるのに死んでいない
Then it becomes like this
するとこうなります
so this is a
これは
used to study cancer is now a very important part
がんの研究に使用されていたものは現在非常に重要な部分です
that could do more cancer research
そうすればもっとがん研究ができるだろう
It's cancer, usually you have a tumor
それは癌です、通常は腫瘍があります
The tumor itself is usually not fatal
腫瘍自体は通常致命的ではありません
We can see news reports that
というニュース報道が見られます。
A certain person has a 20-kilometer
ある人は20キロを持っています。
It can also walk around with this 20 kilograms and live for a long time
この20キロを背負って歩き回ったり、長生きすることもできます。
fine
大丈夫
Unless the tumor just presses on your blood vessels or nerves
腫瘍が血管や神経を圧迫しているだけでない限り
you will have problems
問題が発生するでしょう
What about the most common and deadly cause of cancer?
癌の最も一般的かつ致死的な原因についてはどうでしょうか?
is it shifted
ずれているのですか
It's not just a tumor
ただの腫瘍ではない
Instead, it travels to all parts of the body
その代わり、体のあらゆる部分に行き渡ります
Attack more now
今すぐもっと攻撃してください
that's more serious
それはもっと深刻です
Therefore, a very important aspect of our research on cancer is
したがって、私たちのがん研究の非常に重要な側面は次のとおりです。
Inhibition of asking how this transfer occurred and what it looked like
この転送がどのように行われ、どのようなものであったかを尋ねることの禁止
So someone did this beautiful experiment
それで誰かがこの素晴らしい実験をしました
it puts part of the cells
細胞の一部を入れます
make it express a cancer-causing gene
発がん性遺伝子を発現させる
This is called RES
これをRESといいます
After the performance, this small piece of tissue will proliferate a lot
演奏後、この小さな組織片は大量に増殖します
grow up like this
このように成長します
This kind of organization we call it
このような組織を私たちはそう呼んでいます
and make it express a green fluorescent protein
緑色蛍光タンパク質を発現させます
so you can see this piece
この作品を見ればわかります
It's bright green and grows a lot
鮮やかな緑でたくさん成長してます
but it won't run around
でも走り回らないよ
it stops here
ここで止まります
So this is a normal tumor
つまり、これは正常な腫瘍です
use such a basis
そのような基礎を使用します
Then look for any genetic mutations
次に、遺伝子変異がないか調べます
Let this one tumor start running around now
この腫瘍を今すぐ走り回らせてください
start transfer
転送を開始する
For example, a new mutation is found here
たとえば、ここで新しい突然変異が見つかりました
It will make this group now run to other parts of the body
このグループが体の他の部分に移動するようになります
Take out this piece of cells that will transfer
転移するこの細胞片を取り出します
Transplanted into another fly
別のハエに移植
found that it would continue to run around
走り続けることがわかった
So start this way
だからこのように始めてください
so we can find out which genes affect cancer cells
どの遺伝子ががん細胞に影響を与えるかを知ることができる
Will it transfer
転送されますか
And then you can even screen for drugs
そして薬物の検査もできる
Another one is related to cancer.
もう一つはがんに関連したものです。
This is also a very unexpected thing that happened in basic research
これも基礎研究で起こった非常に予想外の出来事です
He found that if we put such a real organization
彼は、このような実際の組織を設置すると、
This piece will grow into wings in the future
このピースは未来に羽ばたくよ
go and x-ray it
行ってレントゲンを撮ってください
Then do some damage, some cells will die
その後、何らかのダメージを与えると、一部の細胞が死滅します
So these cells with red dots and red dots have changed
したがって、赤い点と赤い点のあるこれらのセルは変更されました
will die
死んでしまいます
So after a while this gets smaller
それでしばらくすると小さくなります
because those cells die
細胞が死ぬから
then you give it time
それから時間を与えてください
it will grow back to its normal size
通常のサイズに戻ります
it makes up for it completely
それは完全に補ってくれます
So this is our body's normal repair of external damage
つまり、これは私たちの体の通常の外部損傷の修復です
What's interesting is that if in an experiment like this
興味深いのは、このような実験では
I'll take an X-ray of it
レントゲンを撮ります
the green half
緑の半分
I express a gene to
私は遺伝子を発現させて、
make those damn cells
あのいまいましい細胞を作る
won't die now
現在不會死
So some
それで、いくつか
damn cell
今いましい細胞
It turns out that this group of cells
この細胞群は、
Blooming now
現在大量繁殖
become a large tumor
大きな腫瘍になる
then from here
それではここから
derived a series of studies
一連の研究を導き出した
the dead cell
死んだ細胞
dying cells
死にかけている細胞
it will send out a signal
それは信号を送信します
tell the next cell to say
次のセルに言うように指示します
I'm going to say goodbye
さよならを言うつもりです
make it up to me
私に埋め合わせてください
So there is an empty
だから空があります
So you split up to make up for me
だからあなたは私を補うために別れた
Then if this group of cells is now
次に、この細胞グループが現在
damn it
くそ
you let it stay there
あなたはそれをそこに残しておいてください
It continues to play such a signal
そんな信号を流し続ける
So the cells next to it have a lot of rope
その隣のセルにはたくさんのロープがあります
Then tell the side
それから側に伝えてください
when we say we cure cancer
私たちが癌を治すと言うとき
Usually you give me a medicine
普通は薬をくれるんですが
kill that cancer cell
そのガン細胞を殺す
the cells that kill
殺す細胞
if not quickly drained
すぐに排水しないと
it actually sends a signal
実際に信号を送信します
Let the next cell grow again
次の細胞を再び成長させます
so you kill the cells
それで細胞を殺します
There are supplements on the side
横にサプリメントもある
So that cancer becomes unkillable
ガンが死滅不可能になるように
So this becomes saying now
だから今はこう言うことになる
cancer treatment considerations
がん治療の考慮事項
a very important thing
とても重要なこと
So you see although fruit flies look
ショウジョウバエは見えますが、
so small
ちっちゃいね
But only on the matter of cancer
でも、この癌のことに関してだけは
It has many important new contributions
多くの重要な新しい貢献が含まれています
the other one
別のもの
let everyone know
みんなに知らせて
A hot topic is stem cells
注目の話題は幹細胞
stem cell is a cell
幹細胞は細胞です
then it will split
それなら分裂するだろう
become two cells
二つの細胞になる
these two cells
この2つの細胞
One of them will differentiate into other cells in the future
そのうちの1つが将来他の細胞に分化する
The other one is himself
もう一人は彼自身です
so he split forever
それで彼は永遠に別れた
He made himself up again
彼は再び立ち直った
so I will never change
だから私は決して変わりません
He keeps producing new cells to differentiate out
彼は分化するために新しい細胞を作り続けます
This ability to self-renew is stem cells
この自己複製能力が幹細胞です
Stem cells often just sit there
幹細胞は多くの場合、ただそこにあるだけです
when we come of age
私たちが成人するとき
Stem Cells Might Stop Over There
幹細胞はあそこで止まるかもしれない
when you need it
必要なときに
it split
それは分かれた
In studies of fruit flies, it was found that
ショウジョウバエの研究では、次のことが判明しました。
Stem cells are influenced by the environment next to them
幹細胞は周囲の環境の影響を受ける
This is the stem cell
これが幹細胞です
it has some cells next to it
隣にいくつかのセルがあります
It will be controlled by certain signals
特定の信号によって制御されます
Then once the stem cell divides
そして、幹細胞が分裂すると、
This stem cell is out of this environment
この幹細胞はこの環境の外にあります
it is not controlled so it differentiates
制御されていないから差別化できる
It can't be differentiated if it's always connected here
ここに常に接続されていると区別できません
so it maintains the stem cells
幹細胞を維持するため
So there are many experiments telling us that
したがって、多くの実験が私たちに次のことを教えています
This Nich is called a seat
このニッチはシートと呼ばれます
It is a microenvironment
微環境です
a small environment
小さな環境
this seat is important
この席は重要です
The size of the seat determines how many stem cells
シートのサイズによって幹細胞の数が決まります
can stay here
ここにいてもいい
Seats got smaller
席が狭くなった
or as you get older
あるいは年を重ねるにつれて
This Nich might get smaller and older
このニッチは小さくなり、古くなってしまうかもしれない
Its ability to maintain stem cells becomes worse
幹細胞を維持する能力が低下する
so we reach old age
それで私たちは老年期を迎えます
Our stem cells also get worse
幹細胞も悪化する
So this seat it can control stem cells of trees
このシートは樹木の幹細胞を制御できるということです
it controls aging
老化をコントロールしてくれる
stay here and go out
ここにいて出かけてください
to form an appropriate proportion
適切な比率を形成するために
it goes out too much
出すぎます
Your stem cells haven't stayed here yet
あなたの幹細胞はまだここに留まっていません
it also becomes differentiated
それも差別化される
it reduces the number of stem cells
幹細胞の数を減らします
so these are very important
これらは非常に重要です
Then this microenvironment will affect stem cells
そして、この微小環境は幹細胞に影響を与えるでしょう
this nitch
この隙間
It was also first discovered in Drosophila
これもショウジョウバエで最初に発見されました
Then some people use fruit flies to study immunity
その後、ショウジョウバエを使って免疫を研究する人もいます
It puts fruit flies on it and puts some of this needle fungus
その上にショウジョウバエを置き、この針状菌をいくつか置きます
Then this needle fungus will infect fruit flies
そして、この針状菌はショウジョウバエに感染します
then grow very fast
それからとても早く成長します
Like this fruit fly, its immune system has problems
このショウジョウバエのように、免疫システムに問題がある
So it gets eaten quickly by the needle fungus
針状菌にすぐに食べられてしまうので、
So the same from here
じゃあここからも同じように
You can then screen for mutations
その後、突然変異をスクリーニングできます
There is no resistance to needle bacterial infection
針による細菌感染に対する耐性がない
or super resistant
または超耐性
Then a series of genes were found
その後、一連の遺伝子が発見されました
What's interesting about this set of genes?
この遺伝子セットの何が興味深いのでしょうか?
It was later discovered that there are also
後からこんなものもあることが判明しました
So this series of human grapes
ということで、この人間ブドウシリーズは
very close to fruit flies
ショウジョウバエに非常に近い
So let's do some research with fruit flies
ショウジョウバエを使って研究してみましょう
So because of this study this
この研究のおかげで、これは
Jules Hoffman in 2011
ジュールズ・ホフマン、2011年
He won the Nobel Prize with two others
彼は他の2人とともにノーベル賞を受賞した
It's also about disease
病気も関係してるよ
it's this fruit fly
それはこのショウジョウバエです
This fruit fly was the first mutation found
このショウジョウバエは最初に見つかった突然変異でした
Then it's called Windless
それからそれはWindlessと呼ばれます
just no wings
ただ翼がないだけ
It has such a mutation that both wings are missing
両翼が欠損するほどの突然変異を持っています
some are missing a wing
翼が欠けている人もいます
like this one it's this side
これのように、それはこちら側です
The wings on this side are missing
こちら側の翼が欠けています
The first gene was later studied a lot
最初の遺伝子は後に多くの研究が行われました
It plays an important role in all stages of development
発達のあらゆる段階で重要な役割を果たします
He discovered that this gene is called Windless in the fruit camp
彼はこの遺伝子がフルーツキャンプでWindlessと呼ばれていることを発見しました
It is found in people that it is called Int1
人ではInt1と呼ばれていることがわかっています
is an early study of cancer that found one
がんに関する初期の研究で、
genes associated with viruses
ウイルスに関連する遺伝子
So this gene was later called Wint
したがって、この遺伝子は後に Wint と呼ばれるようになりました
Take this W and NT
このWとNTを取る
This Wint Passway is very close to the fruit camp and people
このWint Passwayはフルーツキャンプと人々のすぐ近くにあります
It was later discovered that he developed with various
その後、彼はさまざまな症状を発症したことが判明しました
All kinds of diseases are related
あらゆる病気が関係している
So you can even make a book
だから本も作れるんだよ
It is Winds Signaling in development and disease
それは発達と病気における風のシグナリングです
There are many similar
似たようなのがたくさんあるよ
I found it from the fruit camp
フルーツキャンプで見つけました
an interesting mutation
興味深い突然変異
Affects certain developmental processes
特定の発達プロセスに影響を与える
It was later discovered that the matter involved
後にこの問題に関係していることが判明した
his role
彼の役割
are very much related to human diseases.
それらは人間の病気と大きく関係しています。
Another one I saw recently
最近見たもう一つ
Someone did such an experiment
誰かがそんな実験をしました
Studying Diabetes Using Drosophila
ショウジョウバエを使った糖尿病の研究
obesity
肥満
heart disease
心臓病
He gave fruit flies this high-fat diet
彼はショウジョウバエにこの高脂肪食を与えた
fruit flies become fat
ショウジョウバエが太る
a lot of fat accumulation
脂肪の蓄積が多い
this accumulation
この積み重ね
Not only in his fat tissue
彼の脂肪組織だけでなく
will also accumulate to other organizations
他の組織にも発生する
just like people
人と同じように
In this example inside
この例では内部
he will accumulate to the heart
彼は心に溜まっていくだろう
Then the heart accumulates too much fat
そうすると心臓に脂肪が蓄積しすぎてしまう
there will be some diseases
いくつかの病気があるだろう
this lesion
この病変
like human heart disease
人間の心臓病と同じように
a certain kind of like
ある種のようなもの
So you can also use this
したがって、これを使用することもできます
to study some of the heart disease
心臓病の一部を研究するため
so he can find some genes
そうすれば彼はいくつかの遺伝子を見つけることができる
will go
行きます
affect the process
プロセスに影響を与える
In the last period of time, I will talk about this brain
最後の時間でこの脳について話します
We can use fruit flies to study brain function
ショウジョウバエを使って脳機能を研究できる
this is the first one
これが最初のものです
Also a professor at Caltech
カリフォルニア工科大学の教授でもある
Seymour Banser
シーモア・バンサー
He was an important figure in early molecular biology
彼は初期の分子生物学の重要な人物でした
he was born a physicist
彼は物理学者として生まれた
Then he went to study the virus
それから彼はウイルスの研究に行きました
That's a great contribution to molecular biology
それは分子生物学への大きな貢献です
Then to class 1960
それから1960クラスへ
He just said it's done
彼はただ終わったと言いました
Important questions are done
重要な質問は終わりました
so he's looking for something new to do
だから彼は何か新しいことを探している
So he said I'm going to use fruit flies to study neurons
そこで彼は、ショウジョウバエを使ってニューロンを研究しようと言いました
What about the nervous system of the fruit fly?
ショウジョウバエの神経系はどうなっているのでしょうか？
This is our human brain
これが私たち人間の脳です
There are about 10 to 11 times that nerve cells
神経細胞の数は約10～11倍
A mouse has 10 brains
ネズミには脳が10個ある
There are 10 to the 8th power
10の8乗があります
That's all the brains of fruit flies
ショウジョウバエの脳はこれだけです
There are 10 to the 5th power
10の5乗があります
There is also a nematode
線虫もいるよ
Proportionally above
照比例上面
You can't see that point at all
その点が全く見えない
The nematode has 302 nerve cells
線虫には 302 個の神経細胞がある
very precise
非常に正確な
Nematodes are a very special research material
線虫は非常に特殊な研究材料です
we know it very, very well
私たちはそれをとてもよく知っています
but too simple
しかしシンプルすぎる
So fruit flies have 10 to the power of 5 neurons
つまり、ショウジョウバエには 10 の 5 乗のニューロンがあることになります。
Compared to humans and mice
人間とマウスを比べてみると
this is smaller
これはもっと小さいです
Then it is better to study
それなら勉強したほうがいいよ
Then wait a minute to show everyone
それからみんなに見せるからちょっと待ってね
Its behavior is quite complicated
その動作は非常に複雑です
So SIMO BANZER started
そこでSIMO BANZERが始まりました
He said I came to find the mutation
彼は私が突然変異を見つけるために来たと言った
What mutations affect neurological function
どのような変異が神経機能に影響を及ぼすのか
Then he did a lot of different screening
それから彼はさまざまなスクリーニングを行いました
This one is a biological clock
これは体内時計です
It puts fruit flies in a tiny tube
小さな管の中にショウジョウバエを入れます
This fruit fly will walk around
このショウジョウバエは歩き回ります
It has an infrared Motion Detector
赤外線モーションディテクタを搭載しています
to detect whether the fruit fly has holes
ショウジョウバエに穴があるかどうかを検出する
So a hole here is a black spot
つまり、ここの穴は黒い点です
This sidewalk is time
この歩道は時間です
so you just watch
だからあなたはただ見てください
From this line above
上のこの行から
Been going down this fruit fly for a while
しばらくこのショウジョウバエに悩まされています
been in the hole
穴の中にいた
then for a while
それからしばらくの間
almost banned
ほぼ禁止されている
hole again for a while
またしばらく穴
From this cycle is about 24 hours
この周期は約24時間です
So fruit flies have a parity clock of almost 24 hours
したがって、ショウジョウバエのパリティクロックはほぼ 24 時間です
Almost half of the 24 hours it was in the hole
24時間のうちほぼ半分は穴の中にいた
half of it is sleeping
半分は寝てる
Using this letter, it will do the screening
この手紙を使って審査を行います
Then we got three mutants
それからミュータントが3人いる
The first is the Wu cycle
一つ目は呉サイクルです
It can move at any time of the day
一日中いつでも移動できます
The other one is a short period of 19 hours
もう1つは19時間という短期間です
Then one is a long period of 28 hours
そうすると、1回は28時間という長い期間になります
Then the last three mutations were found to be the same gene
その後、最後の 3 つの突然変異が同じ遺伝子であることが判明しました。
that its a different mutation
それは別の突然変異だということ
So the same gene, this gene is called period or per
したがって、同じ遺伝子、この遺伝子は期間またはあたりと呼ばれます
From here, there are many people looking for
ここからは探している人がたくさんいます
These genes affect the biological clock
これらの遺伝子は体内時計に影響を与えます
Then finally find a complex regulation like this
そして最終的にこのような複雑な規制を見つけます
Then such regulation in mice and humans
次に、マウスとヒトにおけるそのような制御
Actually very close
実はとても近い
it's basically a negative feedback
それは基本的に否定的なフィードバックです
It's just my things are slowly increasing
ただ少しずつモノが増えてます
After increasing it inhibits its own generation
増加後は自身の生成を阻害する
it goes down
それは下がります
down to a degree
ある程度までは
it has no way to suppress its own generation
自分自身の世代を抑制する方法はありません
it grows again, it grows again
また成長する、また成長する
so there is a cycle
だからサイクルがある
This cycle is about 24 hours
この周期は約24時間です
So now I know quite a lot about such a process.
それで今では、そのようなプロセスについてかなりのことを知っています。
Our cycles are regulated by light
私たちの周期は光によって調節されています
There is also light that will pass through a certain photosensitive rate of fire
一定の感光性の発火速度を通過する光もあります。
Then affect this passage
次に、このパッセージに影響を与えます
Similar to just now, some people also use that method to study the sleep of Guoying.
先ほどと同じように、その方法を使って国英の睡眠を研究する人もいます。
it has different activities and sleep times
さまざまなアクティビティと睡眠時間があります
Various mutants can also be found
さまざまな変異体も見つかります
From here you can find some genetic influences
ここからいくつかの遺伝的影響を見つけることができます
Then know where these genes act in the brain
次に、これらの遺伝子が脳のどこで機能しているかを知る
So if this goes wrong you won't be able to sleep
だからこれが失敗したら眠れなくなるよ
so start here
ここから始めましょう
Just ask Deputy Wang
王副官に聞いてみてください
how do we adjust the time difference
時差はどうやって調整するのですか
you sleep disorder
あなたは睡眠障害です
how to treat
治療方法
Start here with some
ここからいくつか始めましょう
have some help with this
これについて助けてください
Then someone used fruit flies to learn and remember
その後、誰かがショウジョウバエを使って学習し、記憶しました
Don't think fruit flies are stupid
ショウジョウバエが愚かだと思うな
actually it's not bad
実際には悪くない
That's the first experiment
それが最初の実験です
it smells to fruit flies
ショウジョウバエには臭いがする
you have two flavors
あなたには2つの味があります
You give it a smell first
まずは匂いを嗅いでみると
then give it an electric shock
それから電気ショックを与えてください
inside this pipe
このパイプの中には
you put fruit flies in
あなたはショウジョウバエを入れます
Then the outside of the pipe is the same way
パイプの外側も同様です
so you give it flavor on the one hand
それで、一方では風味を与えます
give it an electric shock
電気ショックを与える
after those few times
その数回の後
it learns
それは学びます
It combines this taste with
この味わいを組み合わせたのが、
Will be linked together by electricity
電気でつながっていきます
then you put it
それからあなたはそれを置きます
From this electric tube
この電管から
move to another tube
別のチューブに移動する
Then give him two flavors to choose
それから彼に 2 つのフレーバーを選んでもらいます
Two flavors one A and one B
AとBの2種類の味
He knows that A will be electrocuted
彼はAが感電死することを知っている
He ran towards B
彼はBに向かって走った
so he can learn
そうすれば彼は学ぶことができる
and he still has memory
そして彼にはまだ記憶がある
because you can live for hours
何時間でも生きられるから
Come back in a few days
数日後にまた来てください
His memory will slowly fade
彼の記憶はゆっくりと薄れていくだろう
so he remembers
それで彼は覚えている
can be found here
ここで見つけることができます
Many mutants can affect this memory
多くの突然変異体がこの記憶に影響を与える可能性があります
Then know these genes
それならこれらの遺伝子を知りましょう
then probably know
それなら多分わかる
this sequence of their actions
彼らの一連の行動
Sure enough, there are other studies
確かに、他の研究もあります
the study of other organisms
他の生物の研究
We can now take this memory
この思い出を今私たちは持ち帰ることができる
into several stages
いくつかの段階に分けて
have short term memory
短期記憶がある
mid-term memory
中期記憶
long term memory
長期記憶
Another memory is anti-anesthesia
もうひとつの記憶は抗麻酔薬
there are some memories
いくつかの思い出があります
If something happens, then you anesthetize him
何かが起こったら、あなたは彼に麻酔をかけます
When he wakes up he doesn't remember that
目が覚めると彼はそのことを覚えていない
Because after the incident he needed to go
事件の後、彼は行かなければならなかったので、
save him
彼を保護する
If you were anesthetized for a period of time
一定期間麻酔をかけた場合
He can't save it, that memory is lost
彼はそれを保存できない、その記憶は失われている
So there are these different stages
これらのさまざまな段階があります
There are many studies to distinguish those different stages
これらのさまざまな段階を区別するための研究は数多くあります
including different mutants
さまざまな突然変異体を含む
Each affects memory at different stages
それぞれが異なる段階で記憶に影響を与えます
So this way we can differentiate it
こうやって差別化できるんですね
That's the distinction we'll probably know by now
その違いは、おそらく今ではわかるでしょう。
at the location of this nerve cell connection
この神経細胞の接続位置で
what kind of changes happened
どのような変化が起こったのか
The mechanism of this basic memory
この基本的な記憶の仕組みは、
after some understanding
ある程度理解した上で
someone to develop
開発する人
Is there any medicine that can enhance memory
記憶力を高める薬はありますか
It is also said that many genetic
遺伝も多いと言われています
sexual intellectual disability
性的知的障害
Those genes are now identified
それらの遺伝子は現在特定されています
Discovery is related to these
発見はこれらに関連しています
So it might also be possible to use
したがって、それを使用することも可能かもしれません
Solve some problems of mental retardation
精神薄弱の問題をいくつか解決する
We now know a lot about the brain
私たちは今、脳について多くのことを知っています
So in a causal brain
つまり、因果関係のある脳では
We know that memory passes through this organization
私たちは記憶がこの組織を通過することを知っています
This is called a mushroom body
これをキノコ体といいます
It's this red and green
この赤と緑です
So it seems like the mushroom has one sticking out like this
キノコはこんな感じで突き出ているみたいですね
Then it can be divided into many cells
その後、多くの細胞に分割できます
We roughly know which cells are in which stage of memory
どの細胞が記憶のどの段階にあるかは大まかにわかっています
what role to play
どのような役割を果たすべきか
Academician Jiang Anshi of Tsinghua University
清華大学の学者、蒋安石氏
he did some experiments
彼はいくつかの実験をしました
he said long term memory
彼は長期記憶と言った
There are two cells here that are very important
ここには非常に重要な 2 つのセルがあります
The fake two cells don't work
偽の 2 つのセルは機能しません
Your long-term memory won't be able to form
長期記憶が形成されなくなる
So we now have a function of these neurons
これで、これらのニューロンの機能が得られました。
Can know very, very finely
とてもとても細かく知ることができる
Another interesting thing is
もう一つ興味深いのは、
Drosophila's Wine Book
ショウジョウバエのワインブック
Someone made a design like this
こんなデザインを作った人がいた
He took many funnels and stacked them together
彼は漏斗をたくさん持ってきて、それを積み上げた
Then pass the alcohol vapor through
次にアルコール蒸気を通過させます
put fruit flies on it
その上にショウジョウバエを置きます
fruit fly trap drunk
ショウジョウバエトラップ酔っぱらった
he just fell
彼はちょうど落ちたばかりだ
If you are not drunk at all
全く酔っていない場合
He is standing on top of the drunk
彼は酔っぱらいの上に立っています
if a little drunk
少し酔った場合
He just dropped one floor, two floors
彼はたった 1 階、2 階を落としただけです
So you just see how many layers he dropped
それで彼が何階落ちたかがわかります
You can tell how drunk he is
彼がどれほど酔っているかがわかります
So there is a very bright observation
したがって、非常に明るい観察があります
The same can be used to screen for mutant species
同じことを変異体のスクリーニングにも使用できます
that also said
それも言ってた
This looks like a wine book
ワインの本みたいですね
Just give him a long tube and let him go
彼に長いチューブを渡して放してあげてください
That also passes through alcohol vapour.
それはアルコール蒸気も通過します。
then you use
それからあなたは使います
this camera to take pictures
このカメラは写真を撮るためのものです
You can analyze whether its steps are messed up
手順がおかしくないか分析できます
can you walk in a straight line
まっすぐに歩けますか
Then here is to see if alcohol is addictive
次に、アルコールが依存性があるかどうかを確認します
It fills the capillary with water
毛細管を水で満たします
there is plenty of water
水がたくさんあります
some water plus alcohol
少量の水とアルコール
Then you can choose
その後、選択できます
Then it puts a different salt
次に別の塩を入れます
So one is blue and one is red
つまり、1 つは青、もう 1 つは赤です
You just eat it last and look inside its stomach
最後に食べてお腹の中を見るだけです
more blue or more red
もっと青くなるか、もっと赤くなるか
you know which one it likes
どれが好きか知っていますか
Let's see if it's addictive to alcohol
アルコール依存症かどうか見てみましょう
There is an interesting experiment that says that
という興味深い実験があります。
If the public courtship is rejected,
公の場での交際が拒否された場合、
then it will drink
それなら飲むだろう
There are two students from Hsinchu Experimental Middle School
新竹実験中学校の生徒2名です。
Come to me for an experiment
実験のために私のところに来てください
he does that
彼はそれをします
they repeat that experiment
彼らはその実験を繰り返します
Turns out they didn't quite
結局のところ、彼らは完全には成功しなかった
After being denied state leave
州休暇を拒否された後
at first he was very depressed
最初彼はとても落ち込んでいた
he doesn't drink anything
彼は何も飲みません
But if at this time he still drinks occasionally
でももしこの時点で彼がまだ時々酒を飲んでいるとしたら
After he drank alcohol
彼はお酒を飲んだ後
he started to like
彼は好きになり始めた
So there are two stages
つまり2段階あります
start with frustration
挫折から始める
and then a sobriety
そして禁酒
Such research is very important
こういった研究は非常に重要です
because all over the world
なぜなら世界中で
especially alcohol or drug addiction in the United States
特に米国におけるアルコールまたは薬物中毒
is very serious
とても深刻です
So you can use this to do research
これを使って研究を行うことができます
The state also has neurodegeneration
この州には神経変性もある
So there are a lot of mutants
だから変異体がたくさんいるんだよ
he has these holes in his brain
彼の脳には穴があいている
Similar to our neurodegeneration
私たちの神経変性に似ています
So these genes are now being identified one by one
したがって、これらの遺伝子は現在、一つずつ特定されています
this is a normal brain
これは正常な脳です
we can also put him
私たちも彼を置くことができます
Take some of these genes that are already known to cause neurodegeneration in humans
人間の神経変性を引き起こすことがすでに知られている遺伝子の一部を取り上げます。
Take it and put it in the fruit fly to express
それを取り出してショウジョウバエに入れて搾り出します
So you see this is a normal fruit fly
これは普通のショウジョウバエです
This is if a human disease-causing gene is put into it
これは人間の病気の原因となる遺伝子が組み込まれている場合です
has become like this
このようになりました
It's basically a lot of cells dying
基本的には多くの細胞が死んでいく
So the red pigment is gone
赤い色素がなくなってしまったので
And then there are these plaques left by dead cells
そして死んだ細胞によって残されたプラークがあります
When you see eyes like this, they become very small
こうやって見ると目がすごく小さくなりますね
most cells die
ほとんどの細胞は死ぬ
So from here we can study neurodegeneration
ここから神経変性を研究できるようになります
There is also a type of picture that is very similar to our epilepsy
私たちのてんかんによく似た一種の絵もあります
These pictures are very interesting
これらの写真はとても興味深いです
It's called BandSensitive like this
こんな感じでBandSensitiveといいます
This is called Knockdown
これをノックダウンといいます
This picture is usually fine
この写真は普通にいいよ
You hit its tube hard on the table
チューブをテーブルに強くぶつけた
it just falls down
それはただ落ちるだけです
Some will start to draw like this
このように描き始める人もいるでしょう
So just like our point display
ポイント表示と同じように
then it's been a while
それから少し時間がかかります
it will slowly recover
ゆっくりと回復していきます
in the process
過程の中で
This sequence is similar to the onset of human dots
このシーケンスは人間の点の始まりに似ています
The process seems to be very similar
プロセスは非常に似ているようです
So this set of these genes
この遺伝子セットは
Many people are now researching
今では多くの人が研究している
Sure enough, the names of these genes are very interesting.
案の定、これらの遺伝子の名前は非常に興味深いものです。
You see this is called Knockdown
これはノックダウンと呼ばれるものです
This is called Eastly Shot
これをイーストリーショットといいます
easily scared
簡単に怖がる
This is Technical Knockout
これはテクニカルノックアウトです
It's a technical knockout in boxing
ボクシングにおけるテクニカルノックアウトです
This is called Couch Potato
これはカウチポテトといいます
it just sits there
それはただそこに座っているだけです
Different kinds
異なる種類
Then our current research on the brain
それから、脳に関する私たちの現在の研究は、
very very fine
とてもとても良い
Then it can be in this brain
それならこの脳内にあるかもしれない
ten to the power of five cells
10 の 5 乗セル
It turns only one of the cells green at a time
一度に 1 つのセルだけが緑色になります
it can draw its this position
この位置を描画できます
where are these extensions of it
その拡張子はどこにありますか
Then it made tens of thousands of
それから何万も作りました
Hundreds of thousands of such samples
数十万のそのようなサンプル
The accumulation wants to know the whole brain
蓄積は脳全体を知りたい
The relative position of each cell
各セルの相対位置
So this is something we'll know soon
これはすぐにわかることです
The structure of the whole brain of Drosophila
ショウジョウバエの脳全体の構造
Then we know the structure of these nerve cells
そうすれば、これらの神経細胞の構造がわかります
to go one step further and try to control it
さらに一歩進んでコントロールしようとする
So someone developed this called
そこで誰かがこれを開発しました
Optogenetics
光遺伝学
it's inside certain nerve cells
それは特定の神経細胞の中にあります
Express some special genes
いくつかの特別な遺伝子を発現させる
This gene responds to light
この遺伝子は光に反応する
so we use a different light
そこで別のライトを使用します
can turn off or activate this neuron
このニューロンをオフまたはアクティブにすることができます
So you can do something like this in the fruit camp
フルーツキャンプではこんなこともできるんですね
This is also an experiment in Jiaen Temple
これも嘉恩寺での実験です
its under the microscope
それは顕微鏡の下で
This has a plate inside and two nuts
これにはプレートとナットが2つ付いています
it uses lasers to track
レーザーを使用して追跡します
have this camera
このカメラを持っています
so it can track every fruit
あらゆる果物を追跡できるようにする
the direction it goes
それが進む方向
Which foot lifts up
どちらの足が上がるか
which wing move
どの翼が動くか
Everything can be analyzed
あらゆるものを分析できる
Then the following may not be able to put
その場合、以下は配置できない可能性があります
it's here
ここにあります
come back
戻ってくる
It's two fruit flies, a bee, and a gnat
ショウジョウバエ2匹、ハチ1匹、ブヨ1匹です
The bee will chase the bee
蜂は蜂を追いかけます
This is normal courtship behavior
これは正常な求愛行動です
It makes the bee close to a certain distance from the bee
ミツバチと一定の距離を近づけます
just give it a pad
ただパッドを与えてください
It's not a pad it's a light burn it
それはパッドではありません、軽い火傷です
Burned, this laser burns fruit flies will hurt
焼けた、このレーザーは焼ける、ショウジョウバエは痛いでしょう
So it will learn that it can't get close to this fruit fly
それでこのショウジョウバエには近づけないことを学習するでしょう
look here it will light up
ここを見てください、それは点灯します
it's too close so light up
近すぎるから明るくして
it goes away
それは消えます
light up again
再び点灯する
you see it and run away
あなたはそれを見て逃げる
After training like this for a while
しばらくこのようにトレーニングした後、
you come to test again
またテストしに来ましたね
Didn't pad him one female and one male
女性と男性を1人ずつパッドしませんでした
If the mother gets close to him, he will run away
母親が近づくと逃げてしまう
look at
見る
so this
したがって、この
The duke will learn and you can train him
公爵は学びます、そしてあなたは彼を訓練することができます
He knew that it would not work if he got close to a certain distance.
ある程度の距離に近づくと効かなくなることは分かっていた。
he will be burned
彼は火傷するだろう
In that case, we can use this system to ask
そんな時はこのシステムを利用して質問してみましょう。
So which nerve cell is related to this matter?
それでは、どの神経細胞がこの問題に関係しているのでしょうか？
So you can decide what kind of neural circuit
つまり、どのような神経回路であるかを決めることができます
to control such behavior
そのような行動を制御するには
That's probably the last example
それがおそらく最後の例です
This is state-run and can also be used to study long pets
これは国営で、長いペットの研究にも使用できます
There is only one state run called Mesucela
Mesucelaと呼ばれる州の運営は1つだけです
this is a
これは
This is a normal fruit fly
これは普通のショウジョウバエです
this is its lifespan
これがその寿命です
cross elbow is time
クロスエルボーが時間だ
number of days
日数
Then how much is the vertical elbow alive?
では垂直肘はどれくらい生きているのでしょうか？
So it's 100% from the beginning
だから最初から100%だよ
Then slowly some die
そしてゆっくりと何人かが死ぬ
eighty days
八十日
just die
ただ死ぬだけ
this is normal
これは正常です
What about the Messerlada fruit fly
メッセルラーダショウジョウバエはどうでしょうか
eighty days
八十日
more than half of it is still alive
半分以上はまだ生きている
that most often survives
それはほとんどの場合生き残る
more than one hundred days
百日以上
So why is it called Messerlada?
では、なぜメッサーラーダと呼ばれるのでしょうか？
because this is
なぜならこれは
oldest person in the bible
聖書の中の最古の人
tell him to live
彼に生きるように言ってください
Nine hundred and sixty-nine years old
969歳
just make an appointment
就約上面
at that time
その時
I don't know if it's exactly the same year as we are now
今と全く同じ年かどうかは分からない
anyway it's documented
とにかく文書化されている
think the oldest
最古だと思う
So this one is called Messerlada
それで、これはメッサーラーダと呼ばれます
that's very interesting
それはとても興味深いですね
it lives long
それは長生きします
But
しかし
and at the same time
そして同時に
It's an anti-tumor drug
抗腫瘍薬です
then it works against muscle
そうすると筋肉に作用します
it can withstand high temperature
高温に耐えることができます
So these resistance to stress are related to longevity
したがって、これらのストレスに対する耐性は長寿に関係しています
there is an important point here
ここに重要なポイントがあります
It's a broken gene
壊れた遺伝子だよ
This picture is to make this gene broken
この写真はこの遺伝子を破壊するためのものです
As a result it grows longer
結果として長くなる
This means that the normal function of this gene
これは、この遺伝子が正常に機能していることを意味します。
to keep you from living so long
あなたを長生きさせないように
So tell us about the design of this creature
この生き物のデザインについて教えてください
You may have passed a useful point in evolution
あなたは進化の有益な地点を通過したかもしれません
you should not go on living
あなたは生き続けるべきではない
So it has a genetic design
つまり、遺伝子設計があるのです
just let you die
ただ死なせてください
Then let's go back and destroy that gene
それなら戻ってその遺伝子を破壊しましょう
You can live longer as a result
結果として長生きできる
And it doesn't just live long
そしてただ長生きするだけではありません
it's still healthy
まだ健康です
Then of course this becomes
そうすれば当然こうなります
Many people are very interested
多くの人がとても興味を持っています
you know this...
あなたはこれを知っている...
this is a receptor
これは受容体です
This is a GPCR receptor
これは GPCR 受容体です
it's on the surface of the cell
それは細胞の表面にあります
So it must be receiving some signal
したがって、何らかの信号を受信して​​いるはずです
So this signal
それでこの信号は
Later, this signal in the body was also found
その後、体内のこの信号も発見されました
someone to design one
誰かがデザインしてくれる人
Inhibition of such a segment of this receptor
この受容体のそのようなセグメントの阻害
a period of ecology
一段生態
PEPTI
ペプチ
Such an inhibitory fruit fly eats
このような抑制性ショウジョウバエは食べる
Its lifespan can also be extended
寿命も延びる可能性がある
Then this gene is also present in humans
ということは、この遺伝子は人間にも存在するのです
So apparently someone is doing it right now
どうやら誰かがやってるようです
How to increase human life span
人間の寿命を延ばす方法
from fruit flies and from mice
ショウジョウバエとネズミから
And from the worms just mentioned
そして、先ほど述べたワームから
Some people are studying these genes of longevity
これらの長寿の遺伝子を研究している人もいます
Discovery of the mechanism of this lifespan regulation
この寿命調節の仕組みを解明
These different creatures actually have one thing in common
これらのさまざまな生き物には、実は共通点が 1 つあります
So do research with simple biology
だから、単純な生物学を使って研究してください
Of course it is more convenient and faster
もちろん、その方が便利で早いです
So in the end it's
それで結局のところそれは
We can use fruit flies to study some things about people
ショウジョウバエを使って人間についていくつかのことを研究できる
including development including disease
病気を含む発達を含む
Traditionally, we depend on the sky for food
伝統的に、私たちは食べ物を空に頼っています。
we filter
私たちはフィルタリングします
These mutations occur randomly
これらの突然変異はランダムに発生します
some is what we want
いくつかは私たちが望むものです
You find the mutation, you find the gene
突然変異を見つければ遺伝子も見つかる
then do research
それから研究をしてください
We can now do the reverse
今ではその逆もできるようになりました
That is, many genes we already know
つまり、私たちがすでに知っている多くの遺伝子は、
maybe from people
たぶん人から
we can target this gene
この遺伝子を標的にすることができます
to create specific mutations
特定の突然変異を作成する
To simulate some human diseases
いくつかの人間の病気をシミュレートするため
From these we can understand
これらから理解できるのは、
The function of these genes
これらの遺伝子の働きは、
Learn about the genes they regulate
それらが調節する遺伝子について学ぶ
Only after you understand these basic things
これらの基本的なことを理解した後でのみ、
Only you have the means to find a way to treat it and change it
それを治療し、変える方法を見つける手段を持っているのはあなただけです
So from here we can get the mechanism of healing
ここから治癒のメカニズムを知ることができます
Strategies for treatment, even using fruit flies to screen for drugs
薬物のスクリーニングにショウジョウバエを使用する場合も含めた治療戦略
fruit flies are fast and cheap
ショウジョウバエは早くて安い
It also allows us to deeply understand the mechanism
仕組みも深く理解できるようになります
But in the end, fruit flies are not people.
しかし最後に強調したいのは、ショウジョウバエは人間ではないということです。
Therefore, the drugs screened out by fruit flies may not be effective in humans.
したがって、ショウジョウバエによって選別された薬剤は人間には効果がない可能性があります。
it has good reference value
良い基準値があります
But the final experiment still needs to be done by people.
しかし、最後の実験は依然として人間が行う必要があります。
Or its not easy for humans to conduct experiments, so we need to use creatures that are closer to humans to do it.
あるいは、人間が実験するのは簡単ではないので、人間に近い生き物を使って実験する必要があります。
It is interesting to give an example at the end
最後に例を挙げると面白いです
This is an old friend of mine Ross Kagan
これは私の古い友人のロス・ケーガンです
He was also the first to do eye development in Drosophila
彼はまた、ショウジョウバエで目の発達を行った最初の人物でもありました。
In recent years, he said that he would come for personal medical treatment
近年、彼は個人的な治療のために来ると言いました
He was a cancer patient
彼は癌患者でした
Then I found your tumor
それからあなたの腫瘍を見つけました
I can sequence and know which genes are mutated
どの遺伝子が変異しているかを配列して知ることができる
Then I put this mutant gene into fruit flies to express
次に、この変異遺伝子をショウジョウバエに導入して発現させました。
So I'm basically replicating your disease in fruit flies
つまり、私は基本的にあなたの病気をショウジョウバエで再現しているのです
So he called this the Avatar of Fruit Flies
そこで彼はこれをショウジョウバエの化身と呼びました
this stand-in
この代役
So this fruit fly has certain mutations
つまり、このショウジョウバエには特定の突然変異があるということです
It fully reflects the condition of that patient
患者様の状態を完全に反映します
Then he targets this person
そして彼はこの人をターゲットにします
These are the fruit flies that are used for drug screening
これらは薬物スクリーニングに使用されるショウジョウバエです
drug screening
薬物スクリーニング
He said I don't want to find new medicine
彼は私が新しい薬を見つけたくないと言った
There are already so many medicines
薬はもうたくさんある
Every medicine has side effects
どの薬にも副作用はある
So medicine often does not mean whether you can kill cancer cells
したがって、薬は多くの場合、がん細胞を殺すことができるかどうかを意味するものではありません
How much damage do you do besides the cancer cells
がん細胞以外にどのくらいのダメージを与えるのか
So he said I'd use a lower dose
それで彼は、私がより低い用量を使用するだろうと言いました
Then I take three medicines and five medicines together
それから3つの薬と5つの薬を一緒に飲みます
Every dose is low
どの線量も低い
So his side effects are also low
したがって副作用も少ないです
Then I thought there might be several mechanisms
それから、いくつかのメカニズムがあるのではないかと考えました
So I heal every mechanism
だから私はあらゆるメカニズムを癒します
So this is for the condition of this patient
これがこの患者の症状に当てはまります
he can do large-scale screening
彼は大規模な上映を行うことができる
Then find a certain combination of drugs
次に、特定の薬の組み合わせを見つけます
kinda like cocktail therapy
カクテルセラピーのようなもの
for this patient
この患者のために
I don't know if this is successful yet.
これが成功したかどうかはまだわかりません。
but an interesting attempt
しかし興味深い試み
And he's in New York, he's looking for that rich guy
そして彼はニューヨークにいます、あの金持ちを探しています
Many rich people get sick
多くの金持ちが病気になる
are willing to invest in such a thing
そのようなことに投資する意思があります
So he has quite a few patients who are currently
現在、彼にはかなりの数の患者がいます。
doing these tests
これらのテストを行う
Maybe soon we will know this one strategy
おそらくすぐにこの戦略がわかるでしょう
will it work
効果はあるでしょうか
This strategy is also due to the fact that in Drosophila
この戦略は、ショウジョウバエでは
You can do it cheaply enough at scale
大規模であれば十分に安価に行うことができます
I will simply introduce to you today
今日は簡単にご紹介します
What kind of research can fruit flies be used for?
ショウジョウバエはどのような研究に利用できますか?
I hope everyone knows
誰もが知っているといいのですが
Why is there a group of people who like to play fruit flies so much
なぜ一部の人はショウジョウバエをするのがそんなに好きなのでしょうか
it's cute
かわいいです
Finally, thank you all
最後に、みなさん、ありがとうございました
Many thanks to our Dr. Sun for his excellent speech
サン博士の素晴らしいスピーチに感謝します。
I've seen a lot of people raise their hands
たくさんの人が手を挙げているのを見てきました
So let's open some Q&A
それでは、いくつかのQ&Aを開いてみましょう
come please
来てください
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
but very sorry
しかし、とても申し訳ありません
The question I want to ask is
私が聞きたい質問は
so
それで
Why on earth did you abandon your wife?
いったいなぜ妻を捨てたのでしょうか？
But what I want to ask the teacher more is
でも、もっと先生に聞きたいのは、
The teacher himself said in the speech that it is very annoying and enjoyable
先生自身もスピーチの中で「とても面倒で楽しい」と述べていました。
But it's been so many years
でももう何年も経ちました
So how does the teacher know when he encounters something he hates?
それでは、教師は自分が嫌いなものに遭遇したとき、どうやってそれを知るのでしょうか?
This is what I will do in the future
これが私が将来行うことです
Then decide what you want to do in the future
それから将来やりたいことを決めてください
How to get over the nasty feeling
嫌な気持ちを克服する方法
I think many people want to know besides me
私以外にも知りたい人はたくさんいると思います
please thank you
ありがとうございます
good
良い
I'm interested in genetics
遺伝学に興味がある
So when I was a freshman in high school, I decided to
そこで高校1年生の時に決意しました。
Do basic biological research
基礎的な生物学的研究を行う
Then I am interested in genetics, so the candidate department
それから遺伝学に興味があるので候補学科
I went to see some departments related to biology.
生物学関連の学科をいくつか見学に行きました。
I'm not particularly interested in plants
植物には特に興味がない
But the heredity of plant lineage is very much
しかし、植物の系統の遺伝は非常に強いです。
They have a lot of lessons on genetics
彼らは遺伝学について多くの教訓を持っています
No need to learn a second foreign language
第二外国語を学ぶ必要はありません
So I chose the plant department
それで植物学科を選びました
In the Department of Botany, I took a lot of courses on genetics
植物学科では遺伝学の授業をたくさん受講しました
At that time, fruit flies gave me the feeling that it was a very traditional thing.
当時、ショウジョウバエというととても伝統的なものという印象を受けました。
decades ago
数十年前
So I went to Caltech
それでカリフォルニア工科大学に行きました
People say that you choose the laboratory
研究室を選ぶのはあなただと言われます
Someone recommended me this fruit fly laboratory
誰かが私にこのショウジョウバエの研究室を勧めてくれました
I will talk about the Seamwater Benser later
シームウォーターベンサーについては後ほどお話します
Then my immediate reaction was this old-fashioned thing
そのとき私の即座の反応は、これは時代遅れのことでした
i have no interest
興味がない
After studying for a few years, I read a lot of these papers
数年間勉強した後、私はこれらの論文をたくさん読みました
I just knew that fruit flies are great stuff for a lot of things
ショウジョウバエがさまざまな用途に最適であることを知りました
Then when I was doing my postdoc
それから私がポスドクをしていたとき
I also want to say that I will return to Taiwan in the future.
また、将来的には台湾に戻るつもりだとも言いたいです。
Think fruit flies are cheaper
ショウジョウバエのほうが安いと思う
At that time, I wanted to say that if I go back to Taiwan and have no money
あの時言いたかったのは、もし台湾に帰ってお金がなかったら
At that time, Taiwan had no money
当時の台湾にはお金がなかった
Just wanted to say you can afford bananas
バナナを買う余裕があると言いたかっただけです
I have a microscope and I can do research
私は顕微鏡を持っているので研究ができます
Then once you feel that the question you want to ask
そして、あなたが聞きたい質問を感じたら、
Using fruit flies is a good material
ショウジョウバエの使用は良い材料です
Those who don't like it will admit it
嫌いな人もそれを認めるだろう
The microscope will make you dizzy
顕微鏡を見るとめまいがする
just learn how to see
ただ見方を学ぶだけ
I watch eight hours a day
1日8時間見てます
Then it got better and better
それからどんどん良くなっていきました
So there's more to do
やるべきことはまだあります
come on the one behind
後ろの方に来てください
please teach me
教えて下さい
It was in the process of the complete metamorphosis
完全なる変態の途中だった
Except for that knot that didn't change
変わらなかったその結び目を除いて
Is there anything that hasn't changed?
変わっていないことはありますか？
such as organs or neurobrains
臓器や神経脳など
Are you perverted?
あなたは変態ですか？
Then the second question is that
それから 2 番目の質問は、
Do householders have any advantages over those in the past?
世帯主には以前と比べて何か利点があるでしょうか。
That is to say, why is he really a developer?
つまり、なぜ彼は本当に開発者なのでしょうか?
Instead of the development book
開発書の代わりに
After this family member mutated
この家族の一員が突然変異を起こした後
growing in other parts of the whole
全体の他の部分でも成長している
I think it works like this
このように機能すると思います
ok what is the first question
はい、最初の質問は何ですか
That's totally perverted
それは完全に変態だよ
this is very interesting
これはとても興味深いです
That is, if he completely knocks out the rework
つまり、やり直しを完全に無効にした場合
You might want to call him a different entity
彼を別の存在と呼びたいかもしれません
He actually preserved his central nervous system
彼は実際に中枢神経系を温存した
His brain is not knocked out
彼の脳はノックアウトされていない
But the brain has also changed a lot
しかし、脳も大きく変化しました
a big change in his behavior
彼の行動の大きな変化
part of his digestive tract is preserved
彼の消化管の一部は保存されています
also changed a lot
も大きく変わりました
But still change him on the basis of the original
それでもオリジナルに基づいて彼を変更します
those cells on the surface of many other bodies
他の多くの体の表面にある細胞
Just kill it and rebuild it
それを殺して再構築するだけです
so it was a very interesting process
とても興味深いプロセスでした
the second is
2番目は
that encore
そのアンコール
Reenactment and solo performance
再演と独演会
Sure enough, there are reprises and solo performances
案の定、リプライズとソロパフォーマンスがあります
There are three solo stars on his head
彼の頭には3つのソロスターがあります
What you see on the two sides is not the same
両側に見えるものは同じではありません
The monocular is very small so it basically has no resolution
単眼鏡は非常に小さいため、基本的に解像度がありません
Those eyes are bigger
その目はもっと大きいです
Then its area can be seen from a very large angle
そうすれば、その領域を非常に大きな角度から見ることができます
Just now there was a very interesting Wang Fu mentioned
たった今、非常に興味深い王福の言及がありました
It's that Guoying's eyes are red.
それはGuoyingの目が赤いことです。
But this red is not a photosensitive pigment
しかし、この赤は感光性色素ではありません
It has about 800 ommatidia in its secondary eye
第二の目には約800個の個眼がある
Each ommatidium is a long tube structure
各個眼は長い管構造になっています
The structure of the long tube is surrounded by pigment cells
長い管の構造は色素細胞で囲まれています
is to express this red
この赤を表現するのが
So light can't get in from the side
横からは光が入らないので
can only come in straight
まっすぐしか入ってこない
This means that it is on a spherical auxiliary eye
これは球の横の目にあることを意味します
every ommatidium every single eye
すべての個眼すべての目
Seeing from a certain angle in space
宇宙をある角度から見る
So as long as the monocular has light coming in
単眼鏡に光が入ってくる限り
It knows from which angle in the space the light comes in
空間内のどの角度から光が入ってくるかを知っています
As for the difference between reenactment and our eyes
再現と私たちの目の違いについて
also difficult to analyze
分析も難しい
But reenactment appeared very, very early in evolution.
しかし、再現は進化の非常に早い段階で現れました。
In the three night insects, that is, inside the painted stone
三夜の虫、つまり塗られた石の中
Trinite bugs have the structure of repetition
Trinite のバグは繰り返しの構造を持っています
In fact, another question is
実は、もう一つの疑問は、
when you fuck him
あなたが彼とセックスするとき
Let's say another pair of reenactments
もう一組の再現を言ってみましょう
Can the other reenactment be seen?
他の再現は見られますか？
Is it a functional reenactment?
機能的な再現でしょうか？
same with wings
翼も同じ
he has four wings can he fly
彼には翼が4枚あるが飛べるだろうか
still he can't
まだ彼はできない
coordinate
座標
Well, I don't know about the wings
うーん、翼については分かりません
probably not good
おそらく良くない
But it's a repeat, it grows on the wings and it's a repeat
でもそれは繰り返しだ、翼を広げて成長する、そしてそれは繰り返しだ
If you poke an electrode in
電極を刺すと
then give him a light
それから彼に光を与えてください
he'll have a reaction, a normal reaction
彼は反応するだろう、普通の反応だ
So that photoreceptor cell is normal
視細胞が正常であるために
It grows in the position of the body, the brain is far away
体の位置で成長し、脳は遠くにあります
So its axis map can't be connected to the brain to connect
そのため、その軸マップを脳に接続して接続することはできません
So your brain doesn't feel the light.
そのため、脳は光を感じません。
The brain does not receive the signal
脳が信号を受け取らない
But just now you also mentioned
しかし、今あなたも言いました
Is its photosensitive color different from ours?
感光色は私たちの色と違うのでしょうか？
Are we red yellow blue or red green yellow
私たちは赤黄青ですか赤緑黄ですか
anyway it's going to fall outside the line
とにかくラインから外れてしまう
it has a green
緑がある
There's a blue pigment and then there's an ultraviolet pigment
青色の顔料と紫外線顔料があります
so different
とても違う
it's not red
赤くないです
There seems to be a problem just now
ただ今問題が発生しているようです
green place
緑の場所
Hello, teacher
こんにちは先生
just put one
1つだけ入れてください
Photos of Cang Ying's state camp chaos
滄英の州営キャンプの混乱の写真
Then its right weight seems to be according to its
その場合、その適切な重さはその値に従っているようです
it has a major axis
それは長軸を持っています
So it was decided when it was still fertilized
まだ受精した段階で決まったので
How does his body plan grow
彼のボディプランはどのように成長するのか
Isn't it just a matter of accepting him?
それは彼を受け入れるだけの問題ではないでしょうか？
I forgot what the name of that hormone is
そのホルモンの名前は忘れました
The effect is that the hormone will also cause fertilization
その効果は、ホルモンが受精を引き起こすということです
It is the structural change inside a single cell
単一細胞内の構造変化です
well this is a very important question
そうですね、これは非常に重要な質問です
There are many people in the state-owned enterprise doing such research
国営企業にはそのような研究をしている人がたくさんいます
It's how the head and tail of your body are determined
体の頭と尻尾はこうして決まる
Let's see before the egg is fertilized
卵子が受精する前に見てみましょう
In fact, his shape is already different
実はもう形が違うんです
So there are fronts and backs and burdens
だから表も裏も重荷もある
So this means that part of the decision
つまり、これは決定の一部であるということです
The body axis decision is already decided when the mother
体軸の決定は母親の時点ですでに決まっています。
how does mom control
ママはどうやってコントロールするの？
Then a lot of genes control this matter
そして多くの遺伝子がこの問題を制御している
before and after
那前後大政
it is consistent with mother's
それは母親の意見と一致する
The back and belly are random
背中とお腹はランダムです
But when the egg was formed
しかし、卵が形成されたとき
These have already been settled
これらはすでに解決済みです
its this egg
この卵です
Does a female eagle have only one egg?
メスのワシの卵は1つだけですか？
or is it?
またはそれは？
it can lay eggs continuously
継続的に卵を産むことができる
Can lay about two to three hundred eggs
約200から300個の卵を産むことができます
it's a lifetime
それは一生です
almost
ほとんど
good nutrition
良い栄養
It can lay an egg in an hour
1時間以内に卵を産むことができる
So it's not the same as a crab
だからカニとは違うんだよ
crab words
カニの言葉
it is soft is one to one
柔らかいです 1対1です
it's one down
一つ下がった
it also has two soft tides
穏やかな潮流も2つあります
also like people
人も好き
It's the one on the left
左側のものです
There is one on the right
右側に1つあります
in this way
この上
come please
来てください
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
I think one problem is
一つ問題があると思うのですが、
the same gene
同じ遺伝子
its on that fruit fly
それはショウジョウバエの上にいます
Symptoms of its manifestation in humans
人間におけるその発現の症状
are different
異なっています
So if we want to study the genetics of a human
したがって、人間の遺伝学を研究したい場合は、
its words for some changes in human behavior
人間の行動の変化を表す言葉
So if we don't see some behaviors of diseases like that in fruit flies
したがって、ショウジョウバエのような病気の行動が見られなければ
presented words
提示された言葉
So how should we proceed with our research at this time?
では、現時点でどのように研究を進めるべきでしょうか？
Yes, now that you are doing research, of course you should find someone who can do it.
はい、研究をしているのですから、当然それができる人を探す必要があります。
So I saw some traits in fruit flies
それで私はショウジョウバエのいくつかの特徴を見ました
Some behaviors can be similar to people
一部の行動は人と似ている可能性があります
Of course the man has something that the fruit fly doesn't have
もちろん人間はショウジョウバエにはないものを持っている
That's actually a lot of people do a lot you can't imagine
実際には、あなたが想像できないようなことをしている人はたくさんいます
Someone uses fruit flies to study depression, avoidance
ショウジョウバエを使ってうつ病や回避を研究する人がいる
That is once you can analyze its behavior
一度その動作を分析できるようになります
A lot of these things actually have similar
これらのことの多くは実際に似ています
So is this similar to the real thing?
それで、これは本物と同じですか？
Still need to do a lot of research to know
それを知るためにはまだ多くの研究を行う必要があります
Sorry, there will be another problem like this
申し訳ありませんが、このような問題がまた発生します
Then if we start from
それでは、から始めると
Some genes in Drosophila
ショウジョウバエのいくつかの遺伝子
and found out that their behavior is different from human genes
彼らの行動は人間の遺伝子とは異なることがわかりました
Then the research value of this gene in Drosophila
次に、ショウジョウバエにおけるこの遺伝子の研究価値
For some of our human clinical medicine
人間の臨床医学の一部について
what kind of contribution
どのような貢献ですか
We're all mostly focusing on that similar part now
私たちは今、その同じような部分に主に焦点を当てています
But it's interesting
でも面白いですよ
Fruit flies are different from people
ショウジョウバエは人間とは異なります
so that different place
だから違う場所
In fact, there are many things worth studying
実際、勉強する価値のあることはたくさんあります
It just doesn't sound very appealing.
それはあまり魅力的に聞こえません。
Especially less attractive for research funding
特に研究資金の魅力が低い
But this is also a difficulty in our drug development
しかし、これは私たちの医薬品開発の難しさでもあります
In fact, fruit flies are far away from people
実はショウジョウバエは人間から遠く離れたところにいます
He said it was 75% similar
彼は75%似ていると言った
the mouse is closer
マウスが近づいてきました
We also use a lot of mice to test drugs
薬物の検査にも大量のマウスを使用しています
People who are useful on mice are not necessarily useful
マウスで役に立つ人が必ずしも役に立つとは限らない
So it's still time for the final drug to be developed
最終的な薬が開発されるにはまだ時間がかかる
still do some clinical
まだ臨床を行っている
Only when the bed experiment is really useful
ベッド実験が本当に役立つ場合にのみ
Are there any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
come over there
そこに来てください
wait a moment
ちょっと待って
can you use the microphone
マイクを使ってもらえますか
You feel
あなたが感じる
That's our research with nuts
それが私たちのナッツに関する研究です
mainly to see
主に見るため
just listen to see
ただ聞くだけ見る
From DNA to infer its influence on disease
DNA から病気への影響を推測する
but if i today
でも今日だったら
just very simple
とてもシンプルなだけ
from a functional point of view
機能的な観点から
For example, I study nuts
たとえば、私はナッツを研究しています
The neural circuits of the brain are healed
脳の神経回路が治る
But we know for sure
しかし、私たちは確かに知っています
Nuts have the same number of nerves as
ナッツには同じ数の神経がある
Complexity and the Human Brain
複雑さと人間の脳
there is a great feeling
素晴らしい気持ちがあります
So if I research today
それで今日調べたら
It's me trying to get the nuts
ナッツを手に入れようとしているのは私です
After the circuit coupon is created
サーキットクーポン作成後
what do you want to build
何を作りたいですか
Functional of human neural circuit
人的neural circuit的functional
It is a functional neural circuit
機能的な神経回路です
how big is the gap
ギャップはどれくらいですか
I think there must be a gap
きっとギャップがあると思うよ
but we think
しかし私たちは考えます
Hope from the structure of the brain of the nut
ナッツの脳の構造から見る希望
how it works you'll learn some basic principles
それがどのように機能するか、いくつかの基本原則を学びます
This principle can be applied to more complex brains
この原理はより複雑な脳にも適用できます
like you go and get a simple computer
簡単なコンピューターを取りに行くのと同じように
Its operation must have a lot to do with supercomputers or related
その動作はスーパーコンピューターまたは関連するものと大きく関係しているに違いありません
So you can make some progress in understanding supercomputers from the simple
したがって、簡単なことからスーパーコンピューターを理解する上である程度の進歩をもたらすことができます。
At least this is something that can be done
少なくともこれはできることです
Now there are many difficulties in studying the human brain.
現在、人間の脳を研究することには多くの困難があります。
So many places have to
非常に多くの場所でそうしなければなりません
Please tell me that I just had that UBX picture
UBX の写真を持っていたと教えてください
Will grow wings Will grow two wings
翼が生えるだろう 2枚の翼が生えるだろう
Is it possible to grow a third set of wings?
3枚目の翼を生やすことは可能でしょうか？
Then ask me how the UBX picture came from
それならUBXの写真がどうやって出てきたのか聞いてください
Thanks
ありがとう
That picture is actually very complicated
その絵は実際には非常に複雑です
Those genes and their regulation
それらの遺伝子とその制御
very very complicated
とてもとても複雑
So just that one picture
それでその一枚の写真だけ
In fact, it is not a picture of a single point
実はこれは一点の写真ではありません
it is several genes
それはいくつかの遺伝子です
Several pictures put together
数枚の写真を一つにまとめたもの
to get that result
その結果を得るために
That
それか
Front
前面
yes it will be longer
はい、長くなります
long third
長三度
No
いいえ
Probably many people have tried to find a way to do it
おそらく多くの人がそれを行う方法を見つけようとしました
So what I just saw was
それで私が今見たのは
Second pectoral knot and third pectoral knot
2番目の胸筋結び目と3番目の胸筋結び目
It is possible to do a conversion like this
このような変換が可能です
The first chest knot is very different
最初の胸の結び目はかなり違います
that so
それはそうだ
it must have some
いくつかあるはずです
This mechanism is blocked
このメカニズムはブロックされています
So you can't activate it
したがって、アクティブ化することはできません
so far no one has found
今のところ誰も見つけていない
I'm very interested in that longevity gene
長寿遺伝子に興味がある
That
それか
you say he
あなたは彼だと言います
When using that peptide to suppress it
そのペプチドを使って抑制する場合
You said it was alive and well
元気に生きているって言ってたね
My impression is that it is like in that place called Xian Chong
私の印象では、西安という場所に似ています。
C.L.N.E.L.E.R. People Go for This Longevity Gene
C.L.N.E.L.E.R. 人々はこの長寿遺伝子を求めています
It turns out that it seems
どうやらそうらしいことが判明
those who do not eat well
よく食べない人
Those who are thinner live longer
痩せた人は長生きする
But you said your vagina
でもあなたは膣だと言いました
Don't talk about gut
内臓のことは話さないで
seems to be very healthy
とても健康そうです
Has anyone tried to find small molecule drugs?
誰かが低分子薬を見つけようとしたことがありますか?
Then I will live longer if I eat one a day
じゃあ1日1個食べたら長生きできるよ
Well
良い
In the article just now, it used peptide
先ほどの記事ではペプチドを使用しました
that's been years
それは何年も経ちました
So I guess someone used
だから誰かが使ったんだと思う
go find little medicine
ちょっとした薬を探しに行く
that small molecule
その小さな分子
uh haven't seen anything yet
ああ、まだ何も見ていない
not yet
まだ
All right
わかった
hurry up or i
急いでください、それとも私が
Ha ha ha ha
ハハハッハッハ
no
いいえ
Are there any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
good if
良かったら
if not we then
そうでなければ、私たちは
Thank you next time Professor Sun
孫先生、次回もよろしくお願いします